bro bro get your rank
back Natural Instinct bro I'd be
mad like no I'd
understand round
two fight oh [ __ ] bro I think he's angry
that I tried to one and done him yeah
he's definitely guys I think he's
angry I I I'm pretty sure he's
angry I'd be angry too not going to
lie
yay oh oh he actually defended
that oh
please I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm so
[Laughter]
sorry round
three
fight I'm
sorry wait he actually blocked us you
know that's when you know he's like an
actual gamer
oh [ __ ] oh my God he's sidestep he
actually knows what he's doing I
literally got here as a
fluke he got his ELO
back he figured me out okay okay this is
why I won and done people cuz like they
figure they figure it out by the second
game all right here
where the lobby at there it
is I'll be in in one
second I'm joining I'm
joining uh all right guys I'm going to
hide the
passcode so it's not my
fault all right guys it's 2250
all right here I
am guys I think this guy learned
though the hor hor what's his name
again the Logan RDJ guy I'm pretty sure
he learned how to counter me okay back
okay
back I'm pretty sure I abused so many
him the thing jig if you so desire to do
so Uncle you may
they're asking if we're ready but none
of you guys are in
here they're ask yeah they're asking if
you're ready but if we're ready but none
of you are hidden
here I'm about to join literally the
only thing I see is slime slime is the
only person here with me I'm a good egg
I'm a good
egg we're going to start with con I
guess I'm coming in I'm coming in I'm
coming in sorry I'm finishing my match
too sorry
after this I need to use the
bathroom got to
hurry oh my God they they kicked out
Logan all right I'm in
ypp all right we got the this this is
your time this is
it this is it wait he do you're actually
this you're actually the same rank at
this as this guy yeah why didn't this
guy rank
up not not have a grind set no grind set
like you what this guy started like a
week earlier than me and it caught up in
three
days that's that possible
here I go it's okay if I lose it's okay
it's all about the
experience and I know my teammates got
me got you
dog waiting for opponent what do you
have to pick get ready for the battle
probably the stage waiting for the the
good random maybe he was timing it he
can time it oh my God it's one punch
man oh he's
serious he's actually
serious how's that coach staying on bro
oh my God cuz he's a kicking guy he's
actually serious now yeah that's true it
doesn't make sense and it's not one kick
it's a great many he already [ __ ] it
up how did
you hey oh my God
so good
yay that Roar with the yay was s
up I want you to know that someone
clipped up please oh my God wait I think
he actually learned though no no no no
no no no no okay okay I should have more
it's only on five it's only hop on
that's true that's
true grab or something
after oh he Ducks now I think like after
what I did to to him he's got he like
learned insane
duck
yes good [ __ ]
nice you're leg you're a [ __ ] legend
that good
[ __ ] unbelievably nuts oh [ __ ] he
doesn't do that thing that abused him
last time you know remember yeah that
string yeah yeah he doesn't do that
anymore cuz I think he he got tilted
that wait what it didn't hit that timing
was crazy it work on purp oh what the
[ __ ] okay okay he was ready for that
round
fight that one oh that was an
accident
what oh no he got
me what how does he do that
doesn't Good crap now Square
oh oh no oh no nice try nice try nice
try good
try he figured me out he downloaded me
from yesterday or today and now we
download back okay what do I do now we
beat his ass what do I do when he knocks
you down it just when he knocks you down
just get up just hold back and get up
instead of uh getting up with a bunch of
uh like 1 2 3 buttons just just get up
with back and just hold back if he
knocks you
down
oh oh my
God he definitely trained against the
king he did not like
that yeah he definitely played against a
lot of
Kings round two good Heavens fight you
don't have to get up either you can stay
grounded if you want oh I should should
I yeah yeah against this guy yeah I feel
like I should yeah this
guy
oh yay oh my God good stuff oh what the
[ __ ] how did that work how that didn't
work he ducked
it he actually
Ducks yeah so you so you run into him
and do the knee to mix it up remember
that running kn
yeahoo
okay wow all right well it worked
y oh
no what a break
yep
oh okay
hooked
yay that's counter hit that's counter
hit oh my god oh what oh he side okay
focus focus
oh he sided
me still alive I hit those let's [ __ ]
go nice
job good [ __ ] oh my God I hit
[Music]
it good [ __ ] I hit those
round
fight oh oh I should I need to do the
square yeah the square yeah CU he a
square that's
right boom boom boom oh he Ducks it now
he blocks it you told me nobody blocks
this you
liar nice try it's all right he actually
learned from
me that's just raw adaptation and a
skull necklace that's true that's true
he was one punch man how the [ __ ] do I
kill that guy I don't think we can yeah
yeah they're going use the
bathroom you got this Con do what I
couldn't do wait doy you have to uh hit
the RAR button before you leave thank
you that was fun
get ready for the next
battle let's get it brother
I hate this
stage it's for
you round
one
fight oh that'ss
okay lot
okay D
okay lots of
grabs I got it
oh wow counter two fight what the
hell
nice nice
wait oh that goes back so far you
forward to one that if you block
that
okay damn they all train against Kings
got it
wow what a swing nice
job can
can my guess is she's starting with k
can cuz her coach shoulder to go the low
on power Crush do you have them pulled
up no it's just a guess okay
okay that' be a crazy intelligence
yeah oh my God hit her out of that
that's crazy
[ __ ] I thought she was dead yeah I
didn't press anything yeah it's free
after angle SL she has her Duke in as
well so be careful no she lost her heat
though she doesn't have heat oh I'm
looking at the other [ __ ] guy
sorry you're looking at
teammate oh my God I punched but all
right got it nice jab nice jab jab
apparently some of my chat said like
uh this team actually exclusively
trained against Kings round that makes
sense and where is it getting them
like I know I didn't
bird doy bird special they never trade
against this
though good job nice work [ __ ] Ki is
Alli kick oh [ __ ] you're right sorry
anyways let's
go
yeah let's go they might have beat my
king but they haven't Beat con's
King
Con you can't Out download him he's
can't canning there it
is oh she's scrambling at a block our
beautiful beautiful patient man
not a good reaction time no
no what I'm talking about dude remember
CH it I remember round that
was that was Unreal
dude that's okay Aly Ki [ __ ]
it
oh nice she's scrambling she's nervous
he lost it round just the snow
he looked at the wrong King the trained
against oh
[Music]
my
grab ah I was going to say cuz her coach
definitely told her to grab first so
expecting grab I'm run up
but ah I'm trying too hard cuz I feel
like she's back there I'm trying to
chase for you can forward who won that
if the face right back flip thing she
had fight okay shining wizard now yes oh
no all good all good
nice good boom wall oh take her to that
wallar wall 6 seven how long can you
go the wake up do it do it again do it
again dude all right just pressure bro
it's just
pressure a real anle here man bro you
should have kept going until she
stopped just keep Aly kicking 100 Aly
Kick n plus one all kick again you could
have done it nice job nice job right
freaky gin
time I taught him that I taught him the
alley
kick
okay well so that time it's your turn
get me in there well con also has to
yeah there it is all
right here we
go oh man can you imagine if this was a
street fighter slam and like the team
had like three Zang GES stupid that team
would
lose badly yeah exactly is that like the
king equivalent no he's a Grappler he's
a Grappler in Street Fighter oh actually
I don't know I feel like lowlevel zeni
if especially on Modern like a Guile's
not going to know what to do like a
first we you know what I
mean same say just last time tell them
to get a street fighter three Hondas
would [ __ ] yeah Honda is a better equip
Honda would [ __ ] people up in a in a
street fighter slam that character is
annoying if you're new round one good
[ __ ] fight make a presence
nice download him
who you know
that I got
it I mean do that but this works
no close though close though crazy I
didn't think I yeah the but would have
been guaranteed round two fight
oh
nice look at the chips Jesus out
pressure we talked about
that wow wow he got a wrong he knew it
nice round
three
fight oh God that was a t
then smack
him okay that was good punish by that
guy Mak
sense nice job
is that true yeah
wow main
character he has the main character buff
that's not fair
fight what is this [ __ ] La what is
this
[ __ ] that's going I'm trying too hard to
he's do he's doing this 214 and he it's
like a high mid mid it's like two
punches and a kick it keeps counter
hitting you it no if he delays it yeah
but he's not delaying
it round
one
fight that yeah that
oh I'm bad I'm bad sorry you'll get used
to
it he plays like a bot like a [ __ ] AI
need to play this is what I said
remember two days go is like he just
plays like the most regular Tekken
you've ever [ __ ] seen yeah so like he
he takes it really slow right yeah he's
not doing a lot oh nice nice punish
yeah oh oh that's what we talking about
baby oh guaranteed that's
crazy oh good you got a big
Le oh my God what a
timing dude I hate this
[ __ ] remember you you have a heat
just burst if it's like the end of the
round and yeah
how does that [ __ ] happen dude I'm
holding back
I all right
start God what
a nice person in real life I [ __ ]
hope
so I think so I think so player strong
player strong player Jen is strong power
no no I'm just I'm just not blocking I'm
just [ __ ]
terrible he gave you a lot of cookies he
whiffed a few times it's okay it's okay
Matt Matt takes it home for us okay I'm
actually losing this one I'm not even
kidding this
unated random [ __ ] E wonder of the
world a religion started because of
him this strongest bot on the planet
save me Jack Jesus you're the equivalent
of an alley
kick he says he'll lose every time he is
so Modesta him praise him start a call
bestow upon the list of your many
blessings oh it's a miracle he keeps
saying he's going to lose and he keeps
win it's Miracle oh my God it
is that's what it is he's going to walk
on water
next oh [ __ ] it's Alyssa
what the [ __ ] I'm speed oh my God Doom
oh interesting what the
[ __ ] let's get it me when
chainsaw oh my
God cool it's cool
still got a
lead round
three fight how do I turn the input in
history
L2 thanks
nice
yeah [ __ ] happen in my armor you pressed
you have to hold it
[ __ ] okay no I mean I mean I should have
uh canceled in bubble I didn't come out
it's all right goat it's all right it's
okay it's okay just one set a lot of
these strings that have these highs in
them
that if you knew about him you could
like her one one her 10 frame punish is
a high high also there's two hits that
go into chainsaws she only uh well I
mean I can't explain it now but just
know there are
gaps good
block oh my God I hate this
guy wow again yeah let's bait out the
Hop kick
then boom
nice what is that move I know [ __ ] Alysa
I hate playing against
her okay
round fight let's get it
nice B nice big
hit take her to the Moon
he does know
yes that string that's a high the chain
okay
okay I L just don't know strength yeah
hey [ __ ] last it on the board not close
at
all fight oh what the [ __ ]
man gross
the [ __ ] this
character [ __ ] I mean that's green but
even yeah we just okay even this this is
going to scale too cuz Alyssa's always
in the air wait really that's crazy
that's so
dumb nice oh nice also in the air what
the [ __ ] uh-oh uhoh oh my God tried to
blast
off the get
fist okay yeah if I'm not that then I'm
not doing
well oh it's over for me
Zoros
no I feel it you turn this
around um dead bro yeah yeah good good
try man I no let's try you know what we
got the loss out of the way got it out
of the
way look thisam hard trained against us
so it makes sense you
know T although the streak is over that
gives us a chance to start a new streak
that's right A Better Way There It Is
there it is it was even longer yeah and
then look at this [ __ ] another [ __ ]
Alysa it's going to go all the way to
Evo makes you
think I can't believe it they went anti-
team
BP I mean they did that last time too
after we won the uh the round robin
everyone train up that's true chat Jack
Jesus fell on Friday he will rise on
Sunday that's true
true it is the Lord's day it is the
Lord's day he died for our sins guys
yeah two round Robins probably hurt us
more cuz this happened to us last time
but round
one fight good [ __ ] o the
so o he is so fast coach you need to
trade us for the
team Jesus oh my God
okay yes sir hell
yeah come on Coach you're
better Oo we
busted fight what am I
doing we're having lots of fun
exactly oh look at her life here for the
wall oh no my God we another oh my God
again
let's go
baby aveng oh my goodness you
are yep yep yep yep yep oh my God all
those
blocksom one day my coach would teach me
how to
block my one weakness oh wow what the
[ __ ] go
the what the [ __ ] yeah we'll work on
Thea like tonight Uncle
Baptist that was pretty good that was
pretty good you know I think it's cuz
like bro didn't didn't coach Matt that
was the
issue he didn't help him at
all didn't get [ __ ] [ __ ] I didn't get
[ __ ] for Alissa I did that myself you
didn't help him at all you clearly knew
how to counter Alysa I literally didn't
get any Alysa I'm not even
kidding I went into replay I was like oh
this is punishable good to know and then
I he purposely did that Matt so he could
look good compar to
you wait what what is this God he
swapped
oh anymore round
one fight oh
I was not expecting
this we're all training for
Alysa okay let's like we don't press
after
that you got two
floors
oh round two fight
nice
oh she came to the
wall oh God nice oh
Jesus Christ oh my
God push back oh my God this is
it I love that kick that's funny that's
funny that he has that yeah like a
specific
back the
[ __ ] that that was her throw break she
tried to throw break but it whiffed
let's get
it I'm going to see it soon guys heal
back oh I saw
it that's a oh that you stepped that you
can't it got nerfed but I didn't my
punish didn't go through
the anym oh my God
what round four you scared of the grab
fight KNE
Loops nice oh my goodness oh my God it
doesn't stop oh it stopped I'm feeling
Justice here hey hey I'm feeling
Justice I sent it in my bones yep hey
[Music]
confident win that was confident dude
that's actually a big win cuz it's Us
and Them between for top two and now
we're even yeah is that real is that
true yeah Tony's number one uh as far as
I know let me see oh no I got them mixed
up with uh myk sorry we got to fight NK
next yeah that's still big that's still
big I Haven got MK and kfm switched up
but still you just need to do well at
MK then we're good to
go oh man he beat me last time honestly
this was sabotage for mat
man if this was tournament you just lost
what does that mean I thought I thought
they
lost what she saying I don't know no it
was 32 that was a coach tiebreaker
wasn't it yeah for the yeah no we would
have won that it was a coach tiebreaker
I don't know what they're talking about
but okay no cuz I won second round yeah
so we yeah that wouldn't happen I don't
know whatever yay
dude all right good [ __ ] I don't think
Alysa players can do math that's what
I'm
saying one more uh one more round
fellas wait they won 32 oh never mind
wait oh no yeah cuz like slime me and
Matt
lost it's two
three we're not we're not used to Matt
losing this is
sabotage if only brro toau that how to
fight against Alysa the only match i l
the on that I literally don't know the
match
up damn the teams are pretty even then
that's wow the king someone in my chat
was like the king players don't know how
to do math
so true it's true they're hating I mean
that's not what their specialty is
[Laughter]
yeah all
right all right one more set fellas One
More set
round fight yes sir
no going to watch myself Lo them YK from
yesterday see what I can do yeah learn
from it I believe you new
coach round
two fight
to be
accurate round three it's okay guys this
is just round robin guys it doesn't
matter the finals is when it matters the
finals is when we're going to [ __ ]
kill everybody it's not our fault
everybody trained against us
[Laughter]
like that's so [ __ ] up why did
everybody hard train against me I don't
know what I'm doing I'm [ __ ] brute
forcing my way into this
tournament
yay
true why are you trading Against
Me In myard
yeah but it's working yeah but like but
like it's not our fault I can't believe
I can't believe people train against us
that's actually so [ __ ]
up that's actually so [ __ ]
up I don't know what I'm doing the fact
that he trained against the king
player and like perfectly countered me
cuz he knew he knew I I only had very
limited set of
moves wait until the Master another
move I can't believe they VOD reviewed I
didn't VOD review I just learn new
[Laughter]
moves it's time to learn a eighth a
seventh move you're right I just have to
learn a seventh move
chat
fight that's all I need to
do oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] I just need to learn oh [ __ ] no no
I pressed the wrong button that's okay
it doesn't
matter because I'm oh okay because I'm
going to grab
her yay round two three kings in a
leading team it's just messed up it's so
messed up okay I hate playing against
this girl because this girl is
anti-grab it's actually crazy
easy like I can't do the tomaha Kake
with her
see but I can't abuse
this
[Music]
yay just alley cake I know that's what I
did
fight oh [ __ ] I didn't expect her to do
that I didn't expect you to do that oh
my God you low kick this how do I get
up she got most of her HP
back you always fall for the other cuz
it's so
stupid it's so [ __ ] stupid I'd fall
for it because of how dumb it is
like it's just so
dumb you win nobody expects it
works every time this is why I won and
done because they realize I only know a
specific set of moves get ready for the
next battle but because it's so low yeah
it's so slow it's it's so slow so nobody
preps nobody expects
it that's so
true nobody expects ready for round
all right here we
go come on oh my gosh she has a
gun I'm not going to [ __ ] kill her
she has a gun oh no oh
no [ __ ] free
chiropractor
yay oh [ __ ]
not yay not y anymore guys not y anymore
guys not y anymore guys it's not yay
anymore guys she kicks she she doesn't
stand up yo
slime does she side step this no what's
up is it ready no what's up what's up
uh dude this is a pretty stressful man
so it's not going to be easy to do this
stuff you just learned yesterday the
next day so I wouldn't wouldn't worry
about it too much honestly [ __ ] the Gin
man it's just like yeah it's definitely
he's annoying character yeah 100% I
think that I was oh counter that I was
just really trying to focus on defense
which is like if you're wrong when
you're defending it's really bad if
you're wrong when you're attacking I
feel like it's it's way more at this
level yeah you would you would dug and
he would launch goodbye to me for three
that axe kick he has yeah and he was
also doing it like kind of raw like I
would go for a grab and he just rip it
and I'm like okay well if I it just
works block a little more cuz they don't
expect it so I don't know I don't know
how much of it was like they just or
this guy's
like he's all right play I think he was
taking some rounds off the M uh
yesterday was it fight I think it's that
about the Fang the Fang way who also
destroyed me so I just got those guys
are honestly I don't think they should
even there should even be in this tier
uh the Fang specifically but uh it's
cool I mean we can watch them like
tonight or tomorrow if you want some
matches if it
helps I think what will help is uh
actually playing like play your gin or
something I can definitely play expect I
told you fine that's what will help we
can do that too I think that if I lose
this it's fine I made a statement she
hates me I might have like if I lose
this I might have lost the game but like
I want the mental Warfare
way sounds like it's actually happening
the way you said it the the tone of the
voice I want a mental War it's all about
exactly she's going to remember this
forever like the
[ __ ] okay you you know she's going to
[ __ ] remember this forever you know
that
the l
k d to
a and I
leave get ready for the next
battle
exactly imagine if that person has been
grinding all her life to be in red Rank
and here I show up I show up and all I
do is this
wait not that wait that's sick how do I
do
that get ready for the next
battle that's myi that's
me that's
me D touched him I [ __ ] two touched
him that's so funny
fight oh [ __ ]
oh my God I tried to block but it didn't
work Jesus
Christ does he duck okay he doesn't duck
okay that's all that
matter I just need to know if he ducks
or
not you're cooking this Bo in a little
bit oh no [ __ ] two touch in the first
game oh he blocks this there's no way he
doesn't he's not that stupid he's in
he's not that stupid oh the charge was
crazy fight oh my God he tried to S step
that but he [ __ ] it
up and he [ __ ] that up I feel bad for
Fe not having his character brother a
lot of these characters play differently
than they used to in
anyways and Fe is literally using
[ __ ] the Evo champ character he'll be
fine he'll be all right is he duck now
no also best of three like y Anything
Can Happen
yay oh never mind not
yet
yay it just works like how you walked
away from him yeah I hate his [ __ ]
weird
get oh wait what that doesn't hit no
more Y no more
y leave me alone I'm
sorry no more
y
round fight Steve's counter hit back one
of his is main oh this guy would die to
back 1 plus 2 HPS 1 plus2 oh [ __ ] if you
can find an
open please let me live please let me
live oh my God
please I blocked it oh thank God he
doesn't
duck
what you said not
duck you haven't done that guard break
setup today no I haven't [ __ ] if you
recognize
wall he ducked I can't believe it he
actually
ducked he doesn't duck until he does all
right guys guys this time we're going to
use this
one day we'll be able to use this one
we're going to be able to use this one
no okay this one no okay I'm going to be
able to do that
soon game is over
brother for the battle all right wait
I'm in a game oh shit's being nice
because he's winning now okay he's being
nice to you no they'll never see it
coming to the oh is this the motion
match wait what rank is he lies round
one
fight all right I got this one yummy um
okay oh my God he actually
does okay oh it's doy maybe she's
AFK no I'm in our
game no I'm sorry don't worry I lose
fast this I'm going to let him have his
ELO oh my my God this guy
actually oh my
God I'm in a game I'm don't worry I'm
going to lose
fast it'll be done
soon cuz that guy's beating the [ __ ] out
of me right
now oh Josh skipped
gol oh yeah he's for this no no no no he
just going to skip while oh okay
okay oh
KO round
three
fight who this is that who Matt has to
play who who's who's that g player oh is
that a
to
who there's a b and gen player in the
lob you got leak
again no oh I think it's the too oh oh
that's Steve oh that's tasty
Steve Jin I thought he played
King that's fine he shows you how good
Jen is I lost on purpose so I can get
in I I say that
also don't worry my my my chat knows
it's right it's
true it's true Chad I lost on
purpose throwing for content
[ __ ] we're
starting yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah almost done no we're actually in
the game
oh getting ready for the
match we're in
in
[ __ ] I'm late for my my daughter's a
recital he doesn't
care I'm going to make it I'm going to
lose for real I lost because they
weren't all there keep looking to the
stands don't see
slime he didn't come damn it watch I
threw the gate because I was so sad not
because I'm
bad all right cook our friend gummy here
okay don't say that cuz now look she
side stepping
me oh my
God bro what the
[ __ ] I thought you said when you're
getting hit like that you just oh is
that that's not a pun no when you hit
like that just hold back wait is that I
can't tell if that's low or mid they're
those were sword slash War mids oh okay
couldn't tell
sometimes okay good start oh oh she
Ducks it's like she
knows oh B good [ __ ] how does she
know oh no I [ __ ] no that's okay doy now
instead of the T you just run and KN her
if you get distance run and KN her okay
that's the X that's the three right yeah
the
okay
um there you go oh my oh my oh my good
[ __ ] okay C Good Start
fight y let's
go you're cing you're this fck yeah I
[ __ ] knew I [ __ ] knew it I knew
it y okay but what if I do that oh my
God
the
alley The Flash
bait back to the ground you go stop
Flying who are you jumping at yeah you
don't have
wings oh no it does have
wings the Supreme Yoshi
mitsu that's counter hit that's counter
hit you hop kick it's fine it's fine
that is so many [ __ ]
never seen more Aly kick in my life oh
my God the doorkeeper special you might
have 200 coaches go me but I just need
one my
God that's a lot of GS bro
round damn is that that IM musician
coaching I don't
know damn that's a little
toxic okay you guys call me broke
yesterday yeah we you're the coach nice
nice
yep only two yes
yes TR oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ] what is she doing
to me oh she block oh damn yeah she
blocked it yeah
okay if she ever jumps she's going low
okay fight
oh oh my God how did I miss that it was
just a little late oh I
see that was
crazy that's my
bad I didn't know he had an
inag nice oh okay okay oh F oh that's
counter hit no that's counter hit
yeah no [ __ ]
good [ __ ] there no
fight what a break sick
break
yeah nice oh [ __ ] I [ __ ] up I [ __ ]
that
up wait what does she do to
me two grab what is that
oh what the [ __ ] how did I miss that
that was crazy doesn't matter though set
up American
reset one more
yes you're so [ __ ] good you're so
good oh [ __ ] she did that
thing hold that wait I hold back though
how
did but I hold back how did she do
that how did she do that nice good how
did she do that [ __ ] scale oh my
goodness like the
scaling yes did I back up no what I H
back
oh just F slow ass
move my legs were up it wasn't
fair oh oh
[ __ ] ra uh RAR RAR ra I quit it I quit
it she did that
thing wait this is no I quit it
rer it's okay it's okay you got it we
got it we got it run your [ __ ]
easy boom
oh the
mix oh no she does that thingy and it
scares me
sometimes
oh oh what the
[ __ ] did I get that that's clean that's
clean hit let's go now I'm scared that
she might do hers though when she wakes
up I don't know I don't know though she
get up to you it's up to you commit or
don't Comm okay we're committing oh [ __ ]
no what how how did not grab she was
ducking she ducked it she ducked it so
we had the running three yeah so we had
the running KNE the three the X
instead yeah he no big deal oh my God
she actually ducked it who would have
thought round well we adapt oh how do we
adapt wait what oh she
nice okay nice leg drop shoulder sh good
yes sir don't duck
yay
okay oh she did that
though I'm scared of
that
yay that's that's
one fight
oh my god when she does that it's
actually so hard to counter
[Music]
sure don't
duck
yay nice
H okay okay beautiful oh I block I think
I blocked it wait what no you m you were
mashing back
three it registered it
yeah yeah might buffer it a i buffered
it
no I mean you have RAR too what oh I
have to stand up after that okay down
down down back
yeah okay all
right
ni
okay
okay oh every time she does that yeah
you have to mash four if you block it
you the right kick the circle to punish
that if you block low mass Circle you
yeah nice hop nice oh I keep my hands is
like it's a
yeah sometimes my hands are in the wrong
position got that one yeah yeah okay yes
yes final final final Final you got it
let's go
doie okay oh I hate that
attack oh no I think she got me from
this
alone
no was close very close very close tough
man nice try nice try yeah tough nice
try it it's just that spinning low thing
spinning one always throws me off yeah
yeah and we'll work on that it's very
easy so for the attorney if we have to
fight her we should be okay it's okay we
got the Intel
now wait do I have to so I to press four
after I block it or yeah so while she's
spinning if you just mash for that extra
kick that comes out won't come out and
you actually hit her M and there's
nothing that she can do to it like that
is like you get free damage from
blocking it oh I
see oh you and J Chen yeah we're back uh
should be a fun one flame ruler
damn got to hit X bro come
on look got this bring it
back I just need to add more
moves bro let's play the game what the
the
heck what ISO doing rage art button rage
art button slime slime slime is he even
here
[Laughter]
Sor oh [ __ ] King ego
match oh my God the king
mirror this is it the king mirror
get ready for the next
battle all right let's cook round
one
fight nice got me ducking
you
oh oh my God
this fighting game player
J this guy [ __ ] playing his fighting
games nice
duck nice
yeah what a ducke
yes yes [ __ ]
yes that's yeah kick him yes Z
kick
round fight that's a one or two break
went after the knockdown con you have to
guess nice
nice
engage wow gamer over
here rushan after
nice yeah he knows
that
round fight mm oh that was good die oh
my God trying to duck him
but nice
break if you block back one to you can
back one to him
back he did it to you earlier it's a
punish yeah
back nice got it nice nice job let's go
go let's [ __ ] go go go final
round
fight [ __ ] I ducked it but I stood up
into it yeah it was counter hit
no oh my God that grab yeah it's he's in
he's in full Crouch during
that Ain no thing wow and con you had
your heat you you with your he yeah he
also didn't use his so right
yeah round one
fight
[ __ ] dude again I'm ducking it but it's
like
delayed
yeah thought he grab I could have just
no
round
two
fight nice bre
thanks nice
kick good
[Music]
duck you're in heon yeah I know no okay
y bigly maybe let's not back one two as
much in neutral but I mean do what
Comfort
fight nice does he not D that no he said
no
oh
[Music]
oh talking
about I'm going learn more knee lader
fight
oh my God
James [ __ ]
yeah what a [ __ ] break
con ah
C okay final round let's go King
nice
oh oh my God cook this man you got this
okay
not what a oh my God
nice that supposed to be a
[ __ ] supposed to be a [ __ ]
grab yo there's no you're [ __ ] legend
for blocking
leg this guy has seven seven wi been
dominating slam but you [ __ ] I cannot
believe you right
now broke his streak that was so
beautifully
clutch let's go I can't believe you bro
I could feel the layers from here man
round one holy fight this
s this is battles
it's like rock paper
scissors [ __ ] okay I didn't know that
like bounced on wall no problem no
problem this one round
two fight nice
oh nice
oh oh what a break break
nice you know what
else
what good you're so clutch you're just
better this is I can't watch this
man this is too intense yeah yes oh oh
good kick
dou
K he don't
know yeah let's [ __ ] go let's go con
yes
[ __ ]
fight the oh the miss oh my God what a
whiff oh do it again oh my God I love
this man I
love you said you're going to buy broker
a drink I'm going to buy you a drink
hello you broke his [ __ ] win streak
yo let's go you killed his win streak
and took the game break his M you mind
broke this man that's the evil
commentator he's seen it all
yeah you you're actually him it just
mixes bro just
mixes
okay all right I'm happy that hey that
was rough though man he would he's
learned some
tricks dude the
uh I'm too antsy with the back one two
like I I got to really [ __ ] stop that
but yeah it's pretty bad but yeah yeah
it it's really but he's got really bad
uh get up Habits Like I know where he
when he's going to stand her duck and it
got more obvious over time so sure sure
scary okay good
sh well
played oh this has to be the most
intense matchup
yet here we
go let's go
slime got this what did what did you own
him with last time that he probably
worked on wasn't he free to like back
one or I can't ones Oh you mean him
sorry he ate a lot of
electrics okay we'll try it until
doesn't work cuz we don't know what he's
labbed and also you know how we labbed a
lot we don't know how much he's retained
either you know what I mean so you can
kind of play your game and we can go
from there
y okay this
guy what a start G round one
fight oh nice
start oops all right
that's all
right oh you had
that
oh we good [ __ ] oh one down five more
yeah round
to
fight that's what I'm talking about
that's some go [ __ ] right
there good blocks
dude downstairs nice off wall
killer had the combo ready and
everything nice conversion beautiful
conversion he's
learning round wow that was sick what
it's cool it's
cool let her get one
string make her feel good you
know
okay do those
pons perfect hop kick
[Music]
too oh he wasn't ready he wasn't
what e why is she walking
[Laughter]
around KO Feast mode activated it's
hibernation
time I'm going to
sleep [ __ ] ghost slime one more dude
three more rounds you got
it round
one fight
okay he's not going to
learn nice
break okay oh remember slime Stone hit
to get out of the wall away from the
wall yeah if you're back on the
wall oh that was nice
stuck that was so sick the frame trap
with the
movement
nice
D keep her on that
wall oh my God the chip Jesus Christ the
infinite
pressure she did not like
that oh nice flip they didn't [ __ ]
know man round
three
fight good [ __ ] up finishing
it that was dude good [ __ ] weight you
knew you KN G whipping [ __ ] like that
you [ __ ]
knew hold this bro hold this the hold
this and that and this and that and the
fish
nice oh my God you broke her block
did she call him
yeah oh my God she's
toxic final
round
fight that's a counter hit yeah the [ __ ]
is that like wild Rising one or
something yeah just frame trap
oh there it was oh there it is
nice big
damage nice power a good power Crush
it's all right it's all
right win I think after wild running 1
plus two bear St he's not going to duck
looking for that grab I think you could
have done another one honestly okay yeah
I think player on the honey bear Sands
mies up and when you back one hunting
bear stance even though that's fake as
hell he will eat the bear stance one
plus two every time round
one
fight yeah that was good with
punish
nice got all that Health back though
nice
why does that
[Music]
work okay me mashing yeah you just have
to hold back round
two
fight SL
C oh she wh
ston head this man at the
wall that
whatever I yeah it was too late I
guess
round
fight
oh look he doesn't even though it's
launched that's
great what a cheat I didn't mean to do
that that looks as [ __ ] though yeah
that's so good that's
good Zone head
baby oh hit me to the wrong side doesn't
matter doesn't matter yeah that be stand
fight that's it nice oh nice hit oh
again R [ __ ]
punish I can't believe you broke that
that was incredible nice that's again
he that there alone that
unblockable yeah you have ra uh nice
it's time he puts pressure on you Rage
that's my read yeah when he puts
pressure on you raage right there mean
like this right this is what you mean
like this like there right
there one more guess right you have a
heat slime keep them
got
him [ __ ] rip that [ __ ] let's [ __ ]
go baby yes that's our bear [ __ ] go
that's my that's our big baby
babyar I [ __ ] I saw it and I I had to
I had to [ __ ] call it out good
[ __ ] [ __ ]
dude we're earning it bro we're earning
it getting it back
man you guys are incredible well done
end in the M
man oh Lord oh the all these matches
have been too they're so [ __ ] intense
all our matches have been it's all the
main stream too it's the big deal dude I
did that unblockable by accident it
might have looked like
BM hey that that's what set up his
that's what like oh man he's going to
just key charge me I'm going to match
and he got that ra for
free all set up this guy's on a four win
streak it's okay it's okay you only lost
to one person you were on an 11 win
streak in Slam technically like across
years hit him on the wall jack
say
shiny yes
sir nice I like it oh L
cute round
two
fight was a good
grab Shining
look it's not fair he has a
gun Jack is a gun
Jack Jack this guy is
gun like these are all gunshots in his
combos why do I keep [ __ ] getting
that [ __ ]
man oh
okay oh my yeah send him to the
retirement
home okay we have to walk that when we
make the read on it we have to walk [ __ ]
is that I expulsion expulsion it's
Infamous oh my
God round
four
fight nice
Reed
oh dropped combo the kill dropped combo
in the kill USA Baby Let's Get It USA he
doesn't know
final round make that Grandpa
retire he doesn't know he doesn't
know he's in the corner there's walls on
each side they're closing
in wake up scar wake up for seven
[Laughter]
years he's dead stop [ __ ] [ __ ]
man round one
his heart St
Midway oh bro counting bro at
one
damn then his
combo like this what a counter
hit oh that was
good
oh time let's go not new time nice
round
two
fight okay God blood was looking at his
shoes
oh he is a gun he is a
gun guys I don't even think we have to
we have we don't have to wait on Sunday
he's back
now uhoh
wave the White Flag
VI no no not there not
there not no not
here I can't believe that be
explosion what [ __ ] no
way what the [ __ ] is that damage that
was a good break by Expos damage oh my
god oh good break
though round four
F
nice mhm oh them see oh my oh my
God the amb it's over it's over in three
games Jack came back that's an infinite
Tech trap okay you have to get you have
to get up correctly otherwise you
literally die it's a miracle that's
crazy what it is it's a miracle oh be
time all right coach all right coach get
him Coach hey I mean that's three wins
against them right's a bad character
yeah but you got you get my
revenge he's good man [ __ ] all right I'm
just gonna play my best whatever happens
happens your best we believe in you you
got it I just just do your best get
ready for the next
battle I'm G close my chat there it is
okay round my God's a polar bear
fight global warming
Israel yeah they're on a boat now
yeah shit's bad the icebergs melted and
he's in Paris
L on that knew
it it right
away show him you're the better mammo
good patience good
duck round
two fight
[Music]
damn
a him no
problem oh nice job good [ __ ] oh
nice
oh oh my shining wizard is isn't coming
out thanks okay is it
wall let's go right his be dick
yeah he's lucky that shit's retracted
make them extinct oh no way it whiffed
what the hell it's the way he stands
with his legs back I
guess I mean I would if I I got punching
the
nuts holy
[ __ ] okay oh my God throw him off the
boat bring
out no it's not that fake [ __ ]
bro that fake [ __ ]
bro nice
nice well done oh yeah that's
guaranteed that was a guer game
situation
round F oh it's cool it's fine fine
coach a little
bit that's
perfect be yeah Slim's taking notes
right
[Laughter]
now might well prolong this match so you
can take more not
beautiful oh broke
that he miss his health sweep his dusty
ass Health sweep we missed it
nice oh no way yes for life for life for
your [ __ ]
life Gusty ass hell
sweep I love you bro bro
let's go I can't believe he didn't duck
there round it's the mental games show
him you're the apex
predator dropped the
leg oh no way it crushes
mids yeah Al kick you love it
nice break that
off there it is boys there's the counter
play nice job holy
[ __ ] oh my God situation to be in I got
nothing but Kuma cake on my
[Laughter]
screen yummy in 4k just I know ass
graphics for free
yeah oh no [ __ ] nice okay we gave him
one round
three
fight this [ __ ] rock paper
scissors backs up okay
look get him back up about it you're not
biting the [ __ ] bait either are
you this is this is such him
Coach
oh oh nice
kick
B [ __ ] I'm talking about one more dude
one more bro it's a turn based game it
is that was
good nice
kick oh wow oh mix happens Happ final
round
[Music]
fight huge oh nice oh
my
nice heing be let's [ __ ] go one hit
oh
watch BL yes crazy to me such a smart
[ __ ] heat
smash oh my God the
bait that's
gone that's a crazy G
CL you were in the air though right it's
not going to be alive yeah I mean it's
still going to take all my gray life
game yes that's what I'm [ __ ] talking