[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
that is in last place is only five games
behind the team that is in first place
I'm muted by the way instead of three
points per sorry I was playing game five
that
is miles's team which is if you for
instance if miles team play Team who's
in first place right now and fiveo them
then they would go from last to First
and braw pro team would no longer in
first place so there's a huge amount of
points on the line today to incentivize
you know playing the first day then
learning and coming back on Friday
playing again and cheating for Sunday so
you'll be playing everybody again today
all of you did this on Wednesday so
you're all experienced and you know how
to do it now we've all done this
together before and then this is your
chance for this is your chance to beat
up the people who got you on Wednesday
and show off the stuff that you've
learned and work with your coaches and
get some new stuff some new data and
it's all worth more points so it's going
to be really important every game is
really really important or the is a ton
of points so good luck out there uh no
pressure right I was about to say yeah
no pressure on almost double it's like
double jeopardy Bas everything is worth
almost double so if you did great on
Wednesday and if you lost on Wednesday
it's time to show all the stuff that you
learn and for do this boom boom boom and
then I do this tonight or tomorrow catch
up with them get ready for f
move the and I think for a lot of people
tomorrow if you're in the LA
area a lot of
people and I do this and I do
this
Chef I'm I think like 10 of us are
probably going I'm not listening by the
way they're talking about set up stuff
I'm
grinding oh
damn I'm I'm on my way to drive over
there hold up make the make the tri but
yeah uh otherwise any questions anything
anybody needs to know or we down the
game if I lose any matches I blame braw
Pro's absence okay yeah I'm with
you what the
hell I ever done to
you
trash I like that that's my teammate
right
there yeah so we we talked about prizes
I talked about it on my stream oh my God
please I can't see is this guy on wi is
it me I can't tell I can't
see Evo for flight hotel registration I
mean you could choose whether or not you
want to enter the tournament that's up
to you if you want to play in Tekken or
some other games of Def
comeer for the teams in first and second
they are from junk food and then we also
have for third and fourth cust
controllers oh God please I'm
sorry everybody in the tournament we we
all sent you Chipotle codes today I'm
sorry if you're in
Canada Chipotle it's fine sorry about
that but we also have chipot we also
have uh something for everybody there's
there's a prize I'll be showing it off
on Sunday but we have something that we
want to give everybody for participating
and then everybody for participating is
also going to get some gift Subs
depending on where your team places so
matter what you'll get something phys
something
digital you can't duck this again cuz
you don't Le
nobody depend on how your team does
today what the EM my fifth move right
here oh [ __ ] okay my move right oh never
mind my God never mind I'm so
sorry game good luck everybody good luck
good luck everybody's leaving
good luck
Gamers
game oh
guys okay and then Boop and then Boop
and then Boop and then and then I can do
it again and then
Boop I love that move so
much fight without him like yelling in
my ear hello everybody sorry
hey congrats on or whatever oh my God I
did it I learned a fifth move and it's
actually coming in
clutch what's your new move what do we
uh the low kick I just Spam the low kick
and then I'm spam the low kick into a
hop KCK oh that's good oh yeah wait do
you have the Hop KCK combo did you
figure that out yeah yeah yeah I figured
it out I learned good I can't wait to
see
it now the question is can I can I use
it in like actual like on our players
you're probably going to get uh
obliterated by
eam hit purple I hit purple everybody
else I think you're good I
think e to try why the [ __ ] is he in my
ELO this man that man should be in the
should be facing slime or you yeah I I I
think they didn't expect him to get good
so fast cuz like it's his first time but
but he comes from fighting game games
like what yeah he's a dork he's a big
dork and he cares a lot which means you
should like put him you know what I mean
he should get like like a handicap or I
should get the handicap
yeah if you if you win one round it's
over exactly if I get one round I win
both sets that should be the hand
cap you guys talking about Shish
man it's not fair why my facing that
guy no he's it you got it what do you
mean she does she doesn't listen she
doesn't it's okay the [ __ ] okay no dude
he's purple yeah what the [ __ ] am I
going to do means nothing purple means
nothing purle means nothing no purple's
really good actually yeah what do you
mean the is it Con purple that's where
really good players
are they're really good though you're
right you're means nothing that means
you mean nothing I think s's going to
mash the hell out of you and there's not
good like law is just buts he's just
going to kick KCK KCK but good luck you
got bro I'm not even going to touch
him no my goal is to hit him one
time you went two three oh wait did I wi
two three I did yeah cuz he couldn't
predict me cuz I didn't know what I was
doing so he didn't know what I was
doing hold on I got to show my chat
something one sec
oh my God please unista
please oh my God I'm missing
up oh my God I I muted myself I got I
got scared I thought I pictured her as
eam even though eam doesn't even play
Alyssa I [ __ ] hate Alyssa
I they're too fast you're too [ __ ]
fast
stop [ __ ] stop someone turn it
off oh God it's okay oh my God I can't
do my
special this so true does anyone know
how much it is to buy tears in this game
like in the battle pass no right you
guys
for batt there's a tulip at level 54
that goes on your head and I could make
myself a Pikmin and I want it real bad
but not if it's like
$300 you know what I'm saying like wait
what how many tiers you have to buy uh a
lot
um let me see we increase battle pass by
20 that's 2,000 tokens if I do that I'll
be at
59 also apparently we're supposed to
join the lobby oh whoops all right one
sec okay I just got here too oh [ __ ]
welcome back coach yo what's up you
should spend your money you should do it
20 Buck Pikmin dude okay but what about
the content you could put that on your
thumbnail you can use as your thumbnail
gu so for your highlights I and then the
tyia I spent how much in Tekken eight
flow my head oh wait no I need it I need
more than that cuz I need no cuz I'm at
29 I need to get to 56 it would be dude
that's expensive it's like 40 bucks holy
[ __ ] you earn it back on your YouTube
highlights you'll earn it back not on
this
video nobody's clicking on that went
crazy uh scar said that he's gonna rip
off his shirt if
he
SE I I have to I have to activate good
timeline sorry it's just I need to see
it
happen Okay okay okay I'm back I'm back
I'm back wait why am I playing against
[ __ ] Sean I don't know wait what okay
I'm going to that's not the match yeah
this is not my
match we didn't train for that guy yeah
I didn't train for him I'm put like
Eddie get ready for I don't know what
I'm doing please play
King okay get in there let's go let's go
I have Eddie locked
in this is stage one two three I never
played this character in my life let's
[ __ ] go we haven't even started this
is a PO fun thing isn't it Kaiser's
Lobby oh my God yeah he's doing that
thing oh I see what you mean stage three
oh my God he's doing that thing I do I
thought you meant like
what oh my God character's gross oh my
God I don't help oh my God this how
people feel what you do that's what you
do that's what I do oh my God no it's
five rounds please please five what is
happening I don't know secret rule set
that I wasn't aware of five rounds of
torture oh my God now I know how other
people feel when they play against me no
it's a test round I don't understand
what's happening I don't know check I
guess
they uh yeah they accidentally made a
lobby with five so they got to fix yeah
oh I've never seen five dots up there
fight how high can it go can can't seven
right that' be crazy that should be the
finals first to seven yeah first to
seven a lot of adaptation going on
there oh my God you know what maybe King
is [ __ ]
holy [ __ ] I mean he's definitely
[Laughter]
good I didn't want people to know how I
my fifth
move I'll run to the bathroom guys I'll
be you right
back round oh they're waiting for you to
say oh okay he went to the bathroom okay
get him 3 three
3 I can't he's just grabbing
me true wow oh my God this is truly
unfair holy [ __ ] somebody Nerf King
please you know we should really ban
this character kic's like you know what
maybe I just play this guy
instead he has a shotgun wait where did
he get the shotgun Hammer it's a shotgun
it's a a cosmetic you can use it once
yeah they're legal in the tournament
wait we should put wait how how do I get
a shotgun don't do not you're not allow
she like stacking her lips like you need
a
license you got four days I'm from
Canada the tournament's gonna be over so
I don't know how it feels I'm from
Canada
I can't believe it he showed me what a
true king player can
do he doesn't even play King what the
[ __ ] I can't believe it guys you know
maybe King is
[ __ ] Chad maybe maybe King was King
is pretty
[ __ ] right to be arms A Mir Cy [ __ ]
yeah wait wait wait who are you
fighing okay back I
am I'm fighting a more I'm pretty sure
right where oh then why join the lobby a
more wait oh right I'm so stupid we're
making a different we making a different
one
oh round yeah five rounds we're got to
make a new one freaking Kaiser man the
heck oh my God you should have been
making the lobby BR Pro yeah but he
wasn't here
fre so unprofessional I was I was
telling everyone that like if I lose any
I blame you for lack of Team support my
moral is so load out now because you
were
late yeah I'm not going to lie I've been
late to pretty much everything my whole
[Laughter]
life I swear dude if I lose we blame BR
Pro hold on I'm just learning something
about you Doki so someone said your fan
base is called drons yeah and then it's
shortened to goons yeah oh
no who whoa whoa whoa whoa who told you
that there there's a double AG in here
whoa whoa whoa whoaa there's nothing
wrong with commanding an army of w
someone say it's a little bit
respectable depending on
how are you are you one of them are you
want are you a are you a he's on the
inside he's on the inside he's on the
inside he's been
gooning all right I'm losing I'm
throwing every single on stop stop
bro oh wait this's dead he got caught
wait what happed the shirtless fight am
I supposed to play I got so used to the
shirt the no
shirt bought some clothes just popped
into a store yeah this is not fair oh
what is this okay oh my God I'm I'm I'm
I don't like this now that she now that
she doesn't have a shirt I don't like
this anymore you guys started right
away yeah I wasn't
there are we supposed to not
start [ __ ] up okay cuz I don't I don't
know anymore the
do
[Music]
yay slow that [ __ ]
down let's go let's go oh my God I'm a
little delayed oh my God he's doing that
thing okay I've never seen that me too I
never seen that either I was like what
ooso oh my God she's doing she's pulling
that off of me
oh no way that hop kicks cuz she bro she
keeps Hop kicking I was supposed to hop
kick this is not fair this is my first
game of the day
okay anyway and now I back up wait
actually no I don't now you go in now I
go in oh [ __ ] oh oh my
God
okay let's go oh no wait you won yeah
yeah I won that I thought you lost that
me too I honestly thought so too I was
so surprised the one more one more one
more okay
okay oh my
God me a little bit
to perfect W you're insane I told you
the fifth move is all it takes we're
getting's go it's the fifth move nobody
expects it it was it was being like
here's a fifth one one and she was
[Music]
like it's like it's like a Zelda game it
comes out of the chest and it's just
your whole game plan now the next boss
got to use it everywhere yeah they've
like planned for four moves but they
never planned for the fifth one they
never it like mixed them up the mental
stack is too high
yeah imagine if I learned a six move get
your ass out of
there said better take off her want a
turn of you want to get in all the king
action you know two two Jaguars and a
bear and
a we're going to Eiffel Tower
slime ah the the Goon accusations truly
truly held weight oh my goodness it
might just be
true where the [ __ ] is where is that
more wait she's God oh no she's over
there get out bro he's
just slime really he's itching man rud
he heard about the he heard about the
King
s he's that guy at the rotation that
like plugs in before anybody asks him
to this is tournament bro he's like yeah
whatever he he takes four Puffs and is
SE taken
like you ever have some somebody go like
is this tournament you're like yeah and
they're like all right and they sit down
anyway like they're going to play after
I what what do you GG shake my head they
tell the T you
one I mean I don't mind if he plays for
me
oh isue oh my God thank you I was like
the six secret move JK I had a secret
six move this is like the Millennia is
naked phase
two the king Scarlet
rot oh
no Wizards this okay the fif move there
we go oh but she uses do that don't do
that anymore don't do that anymore only
that oh my
God yit wait no oh that would have been
humongous okay yeah remove remove the
sixth move stick to the fifth one a a
but it's so
funny you know
what believe keep do you didn't believe
oh my
God why did you
believe my fault my fault it's like
you're play Mama but you put in five
eggs eggs eggs eggs it's the
exactly but he doesn't they don't learn
that's the thing this is a delicious
omelet oh my God they have the answer
and they stopped having the answer I
don't and now they remember it again now
they remember understand why do they
what no no they downloading
me oh what the [ __ ] King versus
King do it yeah okay it's
okay
time
fight yes and I do the six what the
[ __ ] oh my God I don't think that was
that cannot be intentional there's no
way got to go there's no way right
there's no way I did the square oh my
goodness oh no we blocked that yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh but then she did this to me
f f
whatever but she keeps doing she can do
that what what F you know what it's fine
it's all right okay
final round they're both so angry I know
being angry want move number seven move
number seven oh wait but she like
figured it
out she fig she's figuring it out though
what the [ __ ]
h no I mean I
okay
three stop stop
your
stop yes yes what the [ __ ] did it what
the
[ __ ] probably the best Tak match
up it works back wrestling it works what
the hell dude they don't learn I can
keep spamming it as long as they don't
learn that was
insane I don't understand though they
did learn they unlearned they learn stop
they okay it's cuz they think I would
stop doing it but I'm so stubborn that I
kept doing it were so surprised that was
crazy like eventually we'll stop right
but I didn't cuz I was more
stubborn yeah CA all about CA well done
okay I have a real question you get hit
by five alley kicks and your character
is like who the [ __ ] is this guy is that
good I think that's one of your fans in
here leads to a true combo we need some
attention right now we're remaking it
because um because it was first to one
oh eyes are taking two L
already bad lobes wait so I didn't even
even need to win that second set no you
did but you did you did Back to the go
back the
lobby all right nice that was so [ __ ]
easy you got you got your one dub ski I
got my one dub I don't have to win again
I already I already have surpassed sup
record so I don't need to do anything
anymore for
real is the lobby broke for anybody else
yeah it's not yeah it's broken uh I can
try to
make I don't trust your lobbies bro har
give us Waffle House what are we supp
natural we might as well just get get SE
jam and make the
lobby keep having to edit his his code
he keeps posting a Lobby and then having
to edit
it what I can't do it that mean how do
you edit a link like in the Discord he
keeps like posting the link and then
screwing it up he's oh my bad did he
post the right one yeah we have a
password now with the wait all right and
we can show the password to everybody
cuz cuz it's like matter yeah it doesn't
matter we learned that
today all right I'm going to go to the
bathroom while we while everybody files
in one all
right let's
go what did they talk about the
orientation when I was like running late
they were like wow BR Pro's late yeah it
was it was a big they actually did call
you out wait what and then I stood up
for you and said saym has a hair system
which he does whoa I didn't pay
attention I was [ __ ] an fgc like
inside thing that no one talks about but
I'm breaking this News live today all
right he has a hair
system and he's bald in real life nice I
it's not nice no I mean not
[Laughter]
nice oh my God we we already got points
look at me go we're already running it
up ready a positive record all right
guys don't [ __ ] it up now I worked very
hard for that lead let's get it let's
get those five alley kicks I worked very
hard
for points points
points all right if I get on that
goddamn wall stage again I'm randoming
off that's crazy dude do you think do
you think like you could get away with
five alley kicks on
on I might do it I might do it but I
don't think I'm gonna get away with
it for the one time five Al kicks in the
hot
kick I like he's
[ __ ] I was going to say that wall is
so good like if the back is to the okay
thank God we're on Arena okay
fine with me don't you like uh the Dojo
oh cuz the wall who that
Josie round one oh I love the costume
fight yeah that's like beach beach time
Raina oh nice they're both meeting in
Hawaii on the
beach oh my God she's into that Jaguar
dick wait what for
[Laughter]
real gig
agree what a l it's
okay nice wow what I mean oh beautiful
handsome beautiful I see a wall
beautiful a third time I see a wall take
her to the wall Ki The
Wall yes oh the okay so he's sidest
stepping every
time to stop the first
thing I'll pay
attention you weren't paying attention
coach
I sorry there's a lot of people in the
chat oh wow chat over team I understand
I see I see yeah all right
fine I don't know when to get out there
or how to get out one in that
spotle dick Jabs in your
diet yeah we'll be good okay so that's
always going to be a mid that's always
going to be a mid when every [ __ ]
time and I'm trying to just grab to
track it but oh
this oh oh my God oh my God oh nice nice
you got out does he know how to get up
he's ducking he does
not nice yeah he's ducking we're going
to teach you that that's a fre follow
guaranteed damage nice my seventh move
got a side step yeah your seventh move
is a guaranteed
[Laughter]
move fight what a hopc I mean you just
re people like that it's just a simple
Pony oh
nice oh my God I mean talk about
Improvement that's funny as hell lab the
match up re reapply boom dead that e I'm
going to be just like that tomorrow
blocking mids he beat me yesterday just
by Ming if I just like beat that he
might just start with side step again
just autopilot I'm going to see he does
he like his 442 into the high you can d
second hit
of damn oh my god oh nice oh my God the
shoulder we ran the drill we ran the
shoulder drill take it back to that wall
oh my God kick that's all you need
beautiful person I've ever met my life
oh my God that was
perfect top the food pyramid you can't
have too
many but sometimes is a
treat he's he's so good dispenser you're
in his
nice that's all right yeah okay we're
we're setting up for grab a long time
just waiting for me to
stand
oh nice no okay whatever wait wall uh
never mind he might block alley kick
here no oh nice the AL kick hey don't
listen to me man just keep alley
kicking look I didn't listen and I got
my five alley kicks I don't know how oh
my God the shoulder and you just to set
up another knee like look at that [ __ ]
run the [ __ ] over okay they're not going
to get hit by this in two days
that's knee shoulder guarante blocked
the game is over this should have
happened days
ago wrap it up dude this should have
happened two days ago I block your mids
you're not playing so these points add
on to the points from uh two days ago so
this is making the Gap wider between our
team and this team the more they're
worth five points instead of three yeah
oh nice
okay uh all right me wa which team's the
second
team my well the Tony's and nk's teams I
think they were tied for a second
actually so it was very
close nice yeah it's Tony's and W's team
that are the scariest who is this guy
who is this guy the Dron
671 is this not priv wait what the [ __ ]
how did this person get in here again he
was in the last one too yeah yeah how
did this person get in can we not ban
him or kick
him uh I think it's Kaiser all right
there you go do you kick there we go oh
there you go how the [ __ ] does he keep
getting in I don't know how he's getting
in yeah
your Eternal goon oh I got to get
out bro he's hacking the
system all right uh slime remember that
he does a little two hit dance thing he
likes to go low after that's a was
setting four if you block it
okay all right and we finish our Combos
and I mean didn't you beat them didn't
you last I beat him last time but it was
it was clown
world yeah it was I remember it
and yeah he falls for the bar electric a
lot when you just keep repeating it so I
don't know if he's still
will so
ready okay got this man get ready for
the next
battle let's
go I almost wore that same thing
today what he's wearing now round one
that [ __ ] look like a poptart
fight oh my God Beau you're beautiful
that's what I'm [ __ ] talking about
oh I'm definitely behind you
guys he'll be afraid that for
sure round
two fight
what is doing to
me WR
button nice
oh oh that that's good
nice damn it I was trying to run you had
heat slim keep that in
mind oops
round fight oopsie wow I didn't mean to
do that all right I got to F Panic
here
big
oh oh ni beautiful combo really he's
stuck
ohud Corner put in the corner don't let
him breathe
nice round
four
fight what the [ __ ] is this
play I've never seen that large move he
called upon
Zeus that's his uh key it's like a mini
jack nice punish punish that's what I'm
talking about
good [ __ ] [ __ ] yeah the [ __ ] we talk one
more round brother oh my God I'm so
behind we just start with a little hop
fight oh my goodness we're getting real
cute
now that's
okay oh wow [ __ ] crazy no way wow no
way wait did you guys did he win mental
shatter
I'm still watching him beat him
up it's just a reverse 3 like a m in
this opulent Mansion oh
man good [ __ ] man
wow round one
fight nice
all right you're still ahead wh That's
good chip I top
kick oh nice what the [ __ ] is that is
that unblockable yeah it's an
unblockable you can twin pist in him
before he gets to
you yeah yeah
yeah oh nice he missed very nice very
nice
okay round two
fight his large dress like Mr Beast
chocolate Feast Feast Bro Look at Mighty
Feast right now bro Mr spor us okay I
don't know he was just doing he did
neutral air I don't know what that is
right it's Sam here easy beautiful
nice com but it's okay drop your
American reset that's what we call that
slime reset an actual American reset you
guys low
here he
knew you
have oh nice nice flip let's go oh nice
my one more brother this guy learned how
to mix and hunting bear stance it's over
fight
oh that would have been a t right there
close he
dropped I hate him so
pathetic it's a pathetic character yeah
he plays
[Laughter]
pathetically big stop using heat you
[ __ ]
it nice
Ducker okay okay oh okay
okay with
Aon sidewall I've ever seen in my
life ang you got this cool sidewall last
time too I I think it was against him
God that's an actual he fell into the
bear enclosure it just got pushed
and they were like his family was like
oh someone please bro I couldn't get out
he loved Mr
[Music]
Beast oh my God that was so stressful
good [ __ ] D he when he won rounds he
[ __ ] won rounds too it was really
scary L is just kind of steam rolly
he'll do that like he just runs you over
good [ __ ] I didn't use back yeah you
downloaded D slime everything we talked
about bro you are doing that [ __ ] with
purpose I know oh oh it's makes me so
happy bro I'm going to I'm going to keep
it 100 like I know we're having fun but
you're a really [ __ ] good coach like
I'm serious even Beyond like you know
the meme [ __ ] like seriously the [ __ ]
you sent me last night was sick thank
yeah you managed to teach me a fifth
move that's [ __ ]
insane yeah we're cooking oh man dude
get his ass Matt Let's Get It Jack
Jesus real [ __ ] no yakushima
is is a a breath of fresh air for
shifter right
now yeah oh this is shifter uh rage quit
last time okay for him in the Mansion I
think he's like learning now how do you
even get Jack
practice you got to call up Anakin yeah
Red Bull Anakin Red Bull Anakin for $100
an hour this is [ __ ] crazy dude oh my
God Batista bom don't make him unpluged
the beginning of the
round oh no but Ro doesn't know where
he's shooting
yeah
fight oh he's tilted you can
tell yeah I would be pissed if I had to
play
against Jack yeah like he already won
the trip to evil why is he here again
that's what I'm saying his problem man
holy [ __ ]
round
fight oh oh what is that whiff monkey
the
animal Range Five whiff I don't think he
I don't think he's thinking anymore not
going to die that's too much damage
dude he's a big
boy I I'm rooting for shifter now holy
[ __ ] just to balance things out okay he
gets around I got Auto balance to the
other
team oh wait is he going to take a round
off he took a round off you
round fight oh my God okay we are
blocking oh my the that is
insane all he can do is block a
force drop the
don't even need it don't even oh my God
it ended fast it doesn't [ __ ] end
man doy how are you delayed if you're in
the lobby with us I don't know
[Laughter]
weird scaming you're going to have to
like restart I think so
yeah you guys were like end to I'm like
she's still playing doing strings
oh her PC is potato
oh man you know that two hits the string
he did before he did the low heat smash
the second hit is a high round two oh
fight
nice uh-oh big mistake that's in the
Commandments time to be punished half
bar don't let oh my God what a gamma
hell what the [ __ ] is
this it's my
turn it's his turn
forever launch you can
launch why does he have a move that just
like no
reverse ah I like the
idea oh
classic set
up they're killing slime with
that does he know he doesn't
know no way
bounce that's a guard you got to [ __ ]
joking I dude okay it'll be a miracle if
shifter makes it this Sunday I would
destroy my PC this is insane
what his bar go what if like we get the
buy where is his
bar bro what we looked away for 5
seconds and this go is gone two seconds
oh my God two
seconds this is [ __ ] unfair this
character is insane blood where are you
easy blood where are you oh my god dude
I think we ruined his day he has like
four more rounds to
go yeah that's a
yeah that's a
hard how we Face the other four
opponents
oh you know what bro Pro that's a 40
sweep so if you win yeah you got to keep
it keep it going yeah but
surely your king players you let
usach I'm laughing for all you guys
yesterday I don't have time down right
coach like I laughed for four people in
one day when am I going to laugh
me okay we play you me on my way you
said I literally DM you I said hey I'm
having trouble with this you're like go
check the VOD and then you left me
alone I was out I was with slime when
you sent that I'm like people my ass
bro send me on my way you're like n
that's good don't wor you're old here's
$20 order a pizza you're old enough to
take that's what I'm saying that's how
he treats my ass hot dog in the sink
yeah this [ __ ] guy man he
all Matt you call me broke yesterday
it's just payback oh my goodness round
now the chat spams broke Pro like what
is
that
okay
nice [ __ ]
ooh I love that move oh oh oh
nice do the alley kick kick is
guarant yes
oh
yeah round two oh okay I see
fight damn
W it's not a good look if you're the
only one that doesn't win around bro
[Laughter]
not
good the coach doesn't win for us after
all the points we got for him he's late
and he
[Music]
loses wait
unless I'm talking
about let's
go this guy just knows looking like
slime out there
I feel like the more we roast him the
better he does guys
no he needs to prove us
[Laughter]
wrong the
nothing damn he's agile dude the higher
like what the hell the higher level
Tekken gets the more people just run up
do nothing it's so scary you're like
what is he going to do pop pop and it's
game
all right all right all right my fault
coach my fault coach God I'm I'm so bad
at the game it's
okay oh no
RAR no rart we
win oh my God don't worry I'm going to
see the r black
assx
you're he's ring
Kaiser was definitely starting to feel
himself he was like oh watch this St and
then you just wait
wait that's
nice my God I'm so behind good [ __ ] one
more
bro it's okay I'll do my best boys I saw
the rart just then guys round one nice
fight
Boom the coach doesn't know the coach
doesn't know
this is it
uh-oh what a [ __ ] giant swing bro
what send it oh my
God
yes round two he teab bagged
fight that's our coach disrespect that's
our coach that's what Val teaches us I
learned how to teabag from my coach he
told me to do it after every
game please
stop slime you've seen Billy Madison
right yeah yeah we're the odoy that's
this team we're just the [ __ ] Odo
this doesn't bode well to to if we get
to the very end of the movie Let's avoid
B what happens at the end of the movie
what happened don't worry about it don't
worry about it rules rules oh my God out
the air
W wa okay no problem
W oh you got cocky there anti-air anime
fighter
fight
D what the [ __ ] you just kicked her yeah
that's a low grab you got to hold down
back to
Second oh my God all right no problem no
problem here you just wanted to make it
close for content that's it nice oh good
[ __ ] boom
boom punishable and you love a
juicy
imagine
press nice for game [ __ ] is
that oh
what how come we weren't taught that
move it's too dangerous we would kill
ourselves doing
break our neck to power for you guys his
final
technique only when you're a God you can
do
this damn
it CP
oh okay I see okay I see I see oh one
more said come on Coach you got this see
the
Matrix
downloader let's
go let's go round
one
fight one day we'll all be 100
Daniels where the he come from I'm only
30 Daniel not I think I'm 20 Danel how
do you get 100 Daniels they just give
you 70 Daniels after you
oh you get to 30 and they just yeah you
there's just too many Daniels in the
world you got to adopt
them adopt don't
shop oh get up get up coach come on
coach get up they're beating your
assri round come on
fight
oh that oh nice what the [ __ ] is that oh
dude
SM this
dick oh yes sir oh
does she's screaming the whole time
please
stop I hate this oh no oh nice
nice oh oh no she took you to the
wall damn
it no problem no problem
it's okay you bring it back
round fight smash a beer
bottle what a
good
Punisher might be
[Music]
gaming you know we're just giving them
sense of security yes nice what a
counter
okay W everything okay oh we love
holding back here yes yeah we don't hit
any buttons no round
buttons
fight oh my god
oh nice sck
punch oh I didn't know what that second
hit was
oh that was a really good
yeah that might be
it oh yeah damn GG oh
GG's it's okay we just wanted to give
them one extra point you know we felt
bad makes sense yeah you gave us all A
Shard of yourself brawl Pro
yeah across the team because just it's
just mathematically better you know yeah
we add all of us together as one I'm
okay getting carried by my team I'm I'm
okay with that bro it's like the ninja
turtles getting car like Splinter like
taking care of his babies and now he's
the old Splinter and we're the N Turtles
I'm Raphael though I won't be rafhael
that's fine I just Leonardo I'll call it
you
guys sorry sorry that there's to do you
know the Ninja Turtles yeah I'm
Donatello okay there we go that means
that's the party
dude doesn't work better than that
doesn't work out any better it's perfect
perfect I actually liked donatell when I
was a kid cuz I thought he was the
smartest and I thought that was
important yeah that's why I'm Donatella
but not now no now I just I want to be
like the Chad Leonardo with swords sure
sure wait then Matt yeah then Matt is
Mikey Michelangelo that just makes sense
that makes sense literally I I I
couldn't ask for a better Turtle cuz I
know I know he can never be
[Laughter]
donel all right we got St before the
next round so if you guys want to run a
nice we chill yeah I got to do a quick
match I'm feeling kind of yeah I'm going
to reset start my Tekken because I'm 80
[ __ ] seconds
behind yeah you promised you'd hook up
your new computer now you're still on
potato Island in the finals look it's
because it's like those training weights
so when the weights are finally off for
the finals I'm unstoppable yeah right
yeah that's how it goes it's like not 20
FPS you're like oh my God you see the
Matrix I I see an 800
frames that'll be
good uh who's
next I don't know who do we
play we
play against let's look at our team braw
pro chat bro it's or Gau that's
awesome G I'm fighting a uh an Ace
Attorney uh
dragonov he has like the mask and
everything we're fighting tone
next team as box BLX he can beat me
100% I played him a lot last night
yeah how he feel he's getting up there
uh he's getting better for
sure guys I swear for the finals the PC
will be plugged in it's just backing up
I
swear yeah
for real this time for real Chad I would
never lie to you are you watching the
main stream or I'm just on a I'm I'm
quick matching cuz I I feel R here I
swear it's going to be
there but it I'm going to have it set up
before the finals so by the time the
finals roll up I'm going to be a god
king
that doesn't mean she'll use it it's
unboxed the first step is over I
completed the first
step is that what
matters
[Laughter]
yeah I completed the first step
all right this guy's pretty good but his
offense is kind of we frames will be
back soon guys it'll be back soon don't
[Applause]
worry I'm loading in see there you go I
was loading in the shaders I was loading
in I'm loading in more shaders so
confused he ducked that one time but not
other times I don't expect people to mix
up the shaders are loading up guys
there we go it's fine now see now it's
fine now you can see
everything now you can see
everything there that's
fine if he just Waits and then does
that every
time see look it's smooth it's so smooth
chat but this is my favorite move now
this
honestly I haven't done that yet I think
it hits wall here can't let go this is
my favorite move
chat and then I can do the Hop
kick the perfect Moon battle that's how
I got to this
[Laughter]
ELO the best move ever can't stop me
nobody can [ __ ] counter it for some
reason I don't know why hey come on wait
this guy this is guy's on Wi-Fi look
this guy's Wi-Fi he deserves to have the
frames he deserves the treatment I'm
putting him through with my
APC no please I'm sorry I did not mean
that please I'm so sorry I was joking I
did not mean
that all right
oh oh my God goodbye he broke my
arm no see the frames are okay now it's
okay see look everything is fine you
guys can see everything it just takes a
bit to load it in okay watch this and
then and then oh wait what the [ __ ] wait
sir sir you should supposed to let me do
a hop kick that was what the alley kicks
are for oh [ __ ] okay guys it's not
looking so good JK
Boop he duck he cheated ducking in front
of a king player what the [ __ ] is wrong
with
him what is wrong with this
man how dare
you here we
go he's not going to duck again they
never learn they never learn when they
play against a
king oh it's
fine oh wait oh he over here
me it's fine this time it's fine who no
it's not fine I'm so sorry let me go let
me go I'm so sorry let me
go
round
fight there no way and then my secret
hidden six move that nobody knows yet
until the finals then people are going
to know in the
finals that's [ __ ] right no more over
oh [ __ ] oh okay I did not expect that
not going to lie please please please
give me that please
oh give me that one
hit
fight oh oh that's
scary it's fine and then and then it's
my turn right is it my turn it is
yay you [ __ ] you [ __ ] okay it's fine
there you go and again no
he nobody loves you not even your
mom okay I'm so sorry I'm so no no no no
no no no no get closer
[Laughter]
please the sides there you go see we did
it
yay
[Laughter]
yay how did I hit cuz I called him
Loveless I called him a Loveless child
and that's how it hits I'll become a
fighting game
[Laughter]
gamer that's that's how it
works if you tell tell your enemy nobody
loves him they'll get her emotionally
and then you
win no one but ra Hearts For the
Win get one and done exactly he's not
special he's not the only one in
[Laughter]
done it's okay guys guys don't worry I'm
loading in the shade
it'll be fine see I told you it's fine I
had to load in the shaders
there
yay
oh okay nice I don't know how that hit
too but I'll take it yeah oh wait wait
I've never expect people to counter
that we try we trying to say the higher
the eload the more easily I can count
oh [ __ ] okay oh
oh no no
please round
two I'm sorry I'm so sorry JK I'm not
sorry cuz you oh he ducked JK I'm still
not sorry cuz I don't
learn I don't learn
that's [ __ ]
right
yeah okay is he going to hit no he's not
oh it's fine oh he [ __ ] duck that
how how do you oh and he did that too
bro he just walks away you don't walk
away from me oh my God how do you just
walk away how do you lose just turn
around and walk
away okay oh my God oh my God he keeps
he he keeps walking away from me I don't
know what to
[Laughter]
do surprised Pikachu face he
just he just walks it it's insane I
don't know how he does it
the
sping just turn
around you know just [ __ ] turn around
don't duck oh thank God okay don't duck
as well
oh oh nice nice no I [ __ ] it up but
it's for
[Laughter]
perfect I [ __ ] it up but it doesn't
matter
goodbye
goodbye yay we won that the reason why
we're not in a game yet another in the
next round yet is that we won the game
so [ __ ] fast that like uh we won our
set so fast um that we're just chilling
now we're just P warming up nothing
works alake
exactly get ready for the next
we're just waiting how are you so good
cuz I don't need to learn like 20 plus
moves I just learn like four to six and
then just perfect
it you can't predict it because like I
also throw in random Buton mashing so
they can never predict
it cuz it's like which one like they
don't know when like is the real match
you
know if I throw in random button mashing
they can't PR
the
moves oh my God bro
okay oh my God she stopped
it she actually she's going to block
this isn't she
goodbye look she's red rank she she
knows how to do it when I learn a
seventh move I can beat her that's all
I'm saying the moment I learn a seven
mov I can beat her oh my God she [ __ ]
dck
oh my
God just saying the fifth and sixth move
got me to this ELO not going to
lie the fifth and sixth move got me
here
Jesus holy
[ __ ] start throwing out
me yay
goodbye
yay that was so close round
three fight is she going to yeah oh she
is Oh I thought she was going to duck
that's not fair she
didn't why didn't you duck why didn't
you
duck
why oh now you duck okay I didn't mean
now do stop ducking
I didn't mean
[Laughter]
now can't believe
it oh my God now she does
that
[Laughter]
bro why don't you duck when I don't want
you to
duck B
[ __ ] there you
go [ __ ]
off [ __ ]
off um what the heck is a pass code oh
no we're starting oh no
please please I'm getting juggled so
hard right now please please get close
to me that's right
[Laughter]
give me a
sec
yeah leave your ELO I'm going to learn
my seventh move and you're going down
the reds are going down when I learned
my seventh move that's right doi's
coming the red rings you're going down
yay yay yippe all right apparently
[Laughter]
matches I'm like what am I one game off
of red ELO yo team you guys have to join
the lobby no no all right all right
okay I I just beat a red ranker all
right all right all right bro I got a
seven win streak I'm so close I did
promo are you F joking are you on
promo I'm nine points off promo I I'm
going to restart my computer after this
make them wait for us so you can get
your rank I'm literally nine points off
promo that's
insane oh my
God the ears don't go up oh sorry
oh eam does a lot of slide midrange you
remember
that totally
guys it doesn't matter if I show the
password all my other teammates showed
their password already so like I hide it
it doesn't matter my teammates are
showing the password so it doesn't
matter the code is right
here I'm
ready okay so what does eam do again
remember when you played him last time
he did the slide a lot he did the slide
where he it was low from miden I do
block
low I I'm so confused I don't
remember I'm so scared so what do I
do coach what do I
do what wait our coach
left
well left and join s you didn't even
tell me what to do CL chasing as per
usual I
see he didn't even tell me what to
do I can't believe
it I guess I'll never know what to do
our coach went out to get milk guys yeah
he'll come back he come
back'll come back he'll come back to
coaches right
guys he s's not going to know my low
kick he won't expect it
we're just waiting I think we're just
waiting for them
for uh casters to be ready at the moment
chat so we just waiting for now we're
just waiting for
now all right I'm back team sorry they
yed me for an interview
so so what do I
do oh man
um you gotta F okay so if he's mid-range
he's going to maybe do the slide the
punish on the slide might be annoying to
just explain here cuz you have to like
Crouch cancel and then do the down
forward for
Tak wait Crouch cancel
what okay you just when if you block the
slide just Aly kick him three times
that's a punish okay all right I got it
just alley kicking three times I know
how to do that and after the third alley
kick hit hit the Right Punch it's a
fourth hit so that will also okay the
Right Punch okay or you can yeah you can
also just W standing four like if you
block low like then just hit four to do
the was standing four
no he's doing the
thing who's watching this who can
spectate oh my God stop
please the worst part is like I hate
fighting this guy in rank as well too oh
my God you know he's purple he can
duck
round okay you got to hit him with the
elbow the when you're sprinting
okay yeah he knows how to duck so I have
to you think he'll up this yes
oh oh my
God Goodbye cruel
world
Goodbye Oh law is
loud oh my God his ass is just screaming
that's why I'm watching this [ __ ] muted
dude I hate annoying I hate playing
against law in general even in ring
damn it's so annoying oh my God he just
Ducks everything it's like he's been
playing as king player his entire
life hey guys it was great
existing I
existed you
know it went the way I expected it to go
oh
that's all right it's all right he's a
nerd ean's a nerd he wants to go to EV
[ __ ] nerd we already talked about
this he wants to trip so bad oh my God
how does he why do I
fall this character does a lot of stuff
oh yes that's
he let's freaking go
dude wow
that's a mighty ruler there's no wayer
this guy's purple this guy's purple he
lets me alley kick him 20 times like
come on
bro come on talking about that's what
I'm [ __ ] talking about oh no that's
not that's not it guys guys you
J that's TR that's right that's TR you
were live for a while I was it was
actually crazy I've not been alive for
that
long the worst part is like I I hate
being on the right
side hey we're live don't give him the
don't give him the T oh [ __ ] JK I can
pull be both sides I'm ambid dextrous
I'm not though oh my
God what does he do I don't know do you
know I don't know I'm pcking
buttons hell yeah more of them let's go
oh what he blocked that you thought told
me he wouldn't
well if he blocks it then you grab a
after you told me he doesn't block
those hold up it's okay I got that one
round remember I got one round off of
purple you that should be worth that
should be worth some points yeah that
should be like weird one point cuz he's
literally smurfing at this point like
something hey guys I did not exist there
one point give us one point one point
my handicap that's fine that's
fine he's cheating so yeah
honestly the slide seems not fair I
think a Nerf is in
order I think so too I got Hara on the