line I got him on hold cuz I'm busy so
if I can't spectate do I have to restart
the lobby or the game that's so annoying
wait are you the one that who made that
Lobby no I think it was Tony
so you can't even
join
uh I'll just watch on say Jam's stream
don't give me the
view there you're delayed you're delayed
to [ __ ] I'm not anymore restarted my
Tekken I
swear I swear okay you
can't uh let's see here I cannot mine's
up round one
and con
obviously yep we should
thech hell yeah oh I got
that oh my God you bit his dick ah that
sucks
okay remember con you can challenge that
the down two yeah
herey
dragon is blue higher than
purple yeah higher okay not by much oh
my goodness we
labbed let's go with the duck
oh guaranteed at the way is
good yeah I know huge forgot next Alli
kick all kick dude I'm holding back okay
feel like I'm holding back there okay
you got it you got it Island Con someone
said you got
this oh my God a grab
fight yeah oh
yes yes nice attack
nice I don't think that hits oh you're
so good
oh what yeah I didn't think that would
land oh my God that's funny that that
landed R
oh come on
sweetheart he [ __ ]
Tech
wow get him Raz on after back one let go
get him go okay all right cool cool
nice
yeah round
four
fight oh you're such a
goat you know what the [ __ ] to
do nice
oh my God you
press what a [ __ ] monkey what the
hell yeah gorilla why did he he had a
mix he didn't need that all
right
yeah
reverse fight that a go block
oh he's so freaky and
weird really yeah counter
hit okay like I know what to do I'm just
not [ __ ] doing it yeah when that down
two hits while standing for he's mashing
after it yeah okay that was very close
that's the only adjustment you need I
think it's literally just that you
know round one fight not on counter hit
though
yeah oh my
God round
two fight
oh my God God it's [ __ ]
thing dude it's okay okay adapt adapt
round
three
fight yeah oh
God yeah dragon's crazy Dragon St
[ __ ]
yeah yeah I don't know man he just
[ __ ] yeah that's I had I had
something and it's like I don't know
that's all right we run some drills yeah
it's no problem [ __ ] got to play freaky
Josh now freaky freaky ass Josh it's a
whole It's actually an entire freaky
team it's just so hard to
predict it's okay our teammates will win
this for us guys
I
believe this is the second is is this
team second or
third uh second
okay I think yeah yeah this team is
right below us oh but they're tied I
think for a second though if I'm not
mistaken I think like one point above
Kyle Delgato and op yeah I don't know
who this guy is nor do I know who Zin
Mami tensei is that's that's Josh oh I
don't know who K Delgato
is probably just like a streamer guy
yeah just got to kick
him that's
annoying someone kick
Kyle No One's Gonna Play you
[Laughter]
bro someone kick Kyle
wait what's the pass code [ __ ]
919 yeah it doesn't matter doesn't
matter like everybody's seen the
passcode already I bet you can see in s
stream
too Josh man ready up is [ __ ] stupid
he's the stupidest person I think I've
ever met in my whole life ever ran ran
number one on the pr
did someone leak the
code is on screen yeah like what does he
mean wait s actually hides the passcode
oh it's our fault I
guess not my
[Laughter]
screen so we all got a oh God wor and
this is why he's secretly bald
do we actually have to hide the
code look want us to censer the code
somehow I don't have the elements in my
OBS just get a picture like put a white
bar I don't have the
element blackb
bar.png
yeah wait so what how do I how do I get
in
for oh I see I see okay all right we're
going your RAR button brother so
RAR remember slime when he back ones he
generally likes to back one again right
after so you can maybe G that a couple
times and then he's going to start back
oneing into the one two strings which
will beat your GCL so if you're making
the read you can just hold back and be
safe or you can down back four for a
huge call out cuz that'll Crush the high
I think but I mean if you just hold back
against Brian he can only hit you with
his Hatchet and I guess like his um wall
stuff but I mean the depends on the
stage for the wall stuff pretty much
though you know the next battle holding
back definitely more
safe
yeah
y good luck the walls are good for you
as well yeah good luck boss you got this
can bear uh break floor easy yeah round
one
fight good [ __ ] take him to the wall
what a hop kick oh time remember when
he's pressuring you heat burst is a free
get out of jail card for you
okay that not doing that mistake again
round two
fight
what that oh my God Back 2 two one with
a combo back two two
one
oh oh
what oh my God can't believe that
connected that this is bad
it's
okay nice good block Josh all right no
more cell
sweeps BR full crou down forward one I'm
it's safe yep
instead punish
that
oh round three nice fight
breaking that in 100 years a lot of
Chip
nice damn get off the that's a lot of
damage though you don't have to worry
about it
anymore he's going to pop heat and
probably blow heat smash right away I'm
just going to
chill oh my God
there we
go G doing
work let's
[Music]
go
[ __ ]
KO nice good over good overal Josh
fight okay
nice got him nice good [ __ ] got
him Inc I can't
see Theon
job one
more
woo okay that was sick sick though I
just got to
it nice
grab round
one
fight okay
wow good [ __ ] they're
electric [ __ ] broke the another
bounce hell yeah not at that that full
Crouch yeah okay full Crouch down
one I thought he get crazy with it nice
orbital Josh you're such a
goat runs in the room [ __ ] smacks
you ni grab all right no more autopilot
how do I get up and block that I keep
[ __ ] is it or is that true it might
be real I it might I'm not sure I we can
lab it tonight
round you can hit up and
down oh beautiful
T I'm going to see it
soon oh I saw
[Music]
it seconds
fuing
oh he's backing he's
scared what good duck whoa nice
I'm seeing
it one more round one more
[Music]
round round
four
fight nice good job Das guys don't spoil
the ending for me does he win
yet he said not yet locked
in good
job I hate this [ __ ] character in
that [ __ ] stupid move I [ __ ] hate
it it's a good move yeah fight
yes
oh dude
oh it's my fault it's my
fault might kill me
here
wall D I can start command grabbing
more he has no reason to duck after
you're in HPS because you're not doing
the the grab after yeah what I mean so
that's why he's not
ducking you have to threaten the hunting
bear stance grab okay but you got this
you got this in the set if you get the
grab and break the floor it's back to
two one for
fight he just spamming that you just
duck punish that right you can duck it
yes
getting
destroyed round
two
fight
thanks okay oh mhm I'm s back up
oh nice I [ __ ] jabed dude oh I'm so
annoyed and I rolled back into
him
oh so close
round
fight nice
nice yeah focus on
your and to grab all right round got
this
fight what in the
[ __ ] there you go bro back two two one
there it is back two two one and
twice okay that's fine there you you
need that that's going to force your mix
dude there you go good [ __ ] nice that's
two in a
row round
fight oh that was bad I got to do the
command
grab nice orbital
winable
very I think I'm dead here I dead ass
rarded too so a that's close that's okay
last round super close I mean like final
final right like last
time I hate losing to him so much
ha losing
Josh oh God go to his def yourself in go
to his room right now no the thing is I
would never I would never pop off like
he popped off that's the difference
that's the that's the Pepsi difference
the Pepsi difference what is that God
he's so miserable to lose against oh my
God I'm losing
mine oh he's giving me props that's
really cool was he giving me props when
he went
[Laughter]
[ __ ] it's okay here to redeem
us oh this dude boxbox is hella random
bro what the Yeah you got a mission you
haven't that picture
bro you got redeem got it man I don't
know dud this so [ __ ] random say that
every time and you win every
time notes for
Brian
F round
one
fight yeah I all
that whoa whoa whoa not that move bro
[Music]
okay oh all right that's
one round
two
fight
nice yeah that's crazy that that LS oh
my God this uh this stage a good Jack
stage
too so we got like good RNG good
rotation yeah
definitely round another rotation oh not
fully get
rotated did you pick this stage on
purpose or was it random oh [ __ ] oh we
blocked this oh F I forgot that Oscar's
[ __ ] no we blocked it
it's oh
nice I I just saw him block
[Music]
it [ __ ]
okay don't let us get
[Laughter]
swept have BR we still have
him uh don't rely on me I'm coming off
an
L there's no way
[Music]
a that's too much damage Jesus there
should be more because there's a wall
there [ __ ] no way oh my God that's the
criminal character H this we need this
we need this oh my God that to Joe Crush
shout out to Joe Crush bro car my ass
I hate that so much you have no
idea oh my God
what oh
really okay never do that to
B yeah F signifier
Slayer yeah he came back from that [ __ ]
oh [ __ ] box box bro what the [ __ ] is
he doing to you I don't
know oh my god oh he's locking it in
that's all right that's all right fight
got to make it
close see
the oh my God yeah that was a nice delay
for his dog
oh I can't K
Jesus sh nuts only King has missile
hands he'll be
perfect he really reacts to that that's
crazy for new
newer Jesus
don't let him stand up keep him on the
floor how does he do it yeah fuckinge
dude let's go fuing [ __ ]
go just when you think he's at his
lowest it's a miracle it's a miracle
slightly more
correct grab because I can't take grab
we didn't get sweat guys thank God thank
God Matt did it he saved us always a
Miracle's tough
man yeah I mean there's a there's a
reason they're top top right now right
yeah they're right below us he was
playing hella good too but he like he
wasn't optimizing but he was like doing
pretty good yeah not good
enough touching man you guess wrong
twice and you die
yeah all right we got our Five Points
yippee yeah good job guys
get ready for Coach you got this redeem
us too the
sequel I'll just play my
best round
one
fight good [ __ ] nice
dud oh my God take him to the
wall
perfect round two he's pressing
fight that's my [ __ ] coach oh my
oh oh you can't ra after CU
SM scary
yeah round
three
fight come on
yes good
[ __ ]
nice yes
sir good [ __ ]
nice end it with an alley kick fight for
the fans for the fans people in the
back i' been hitting him with a lot of
mids so I'm surprised he's
ducking imine it's cuz he sees King he
automatic Ducks because of
[Music]
it that wall
was
yeah think he broke the
wall fight
oh oh man that
sucks D the dick move nice try nice try
got this coach yeah you got the second
set theall
round
one
fight
nice good
[ __ ] oh [ __ ]
no we're
jining oh oh muscle Buster the muscle
Buster close Brian freaky Brian does
that hurt freaky Brian does it hurt
freaky Brian
to
fight it's hard to hit confirm when that
down forward two connects but and it
hits guys are smoing man yes yeah he's
like
dancing it's like those YouTube videos
are like perfect it's in the
wall oh Jesus
Christ a dude he's good at this
yeah feel like he's training
specifically against
Kings
Mario I cannot believe you got away with
that [ __ ]
F back fback SM that's the mango that's
the mango the
mango nice okay oh that's a lot that's a
lot of damage oh my God the Jagger run
nothing this is too scary I I can't yeah
had the sudden
pause
oh break his leg break it bro
ouch Sharpshooter okay are you going to
rotate him
there's been so many people rotated
today
yeah thing about freaky Brian is he like
it oh big hop
kick oh should be everything Dash oh ni
try ni try Dam it's a hard
combo oh I wish I hit that round
four fight
oh he tched it oh King
SMH
nice all the sidewall adjustment side
adjust is crazy here you're
nuts oh my music [ __ ] popping
off I got Rebel hanger final round
playing oh wow
woo oh that's
scary oh he's clutching he's
clutching round get a monk get a monk
come on coach
nice what a [ __ ]
Dodge oh why did
he this is a bad spot to be
in that's the dick move Oh that's oh
that's no
way d nice
ni oh my God he's very clutch
Jesus hey I mean like didn't get sweep
hey I didn't get sweep you're we need
yeah we needed that we need that real
bad oh that guy is really good [ __ ]
mhm that guy was insane let's just hope
that one of the teams beat them I know
tone really really really wants to win
too like he wanted me on his team and
[ __ ] like he was like
hey would it be cool if you're on my
team
I oh my gosh we're definitely going to
see them they're definitely getting one
of the buys I feel oh yeah 100% I think
it's going to be between us and NK te
we're just trying to get the other one
yeah I [ __ ] love that dude that the
turtle
tweet my God that one was intense that
felt like the finals
oh did you guys see the hard team's over
hard team's over the bra Pro
chat ouram in theing
hilarious yeah that was that was kind of
funny that was
good damn losing kind of sucks oh my God
losing sucks dude
my God that's why we're
competitors we lose now so we get
motivated to win you you have like so
many so much advice in the chat and you
just don't want to read any of it either
you know I know cuz you want to walk in
and [ __ ] like oh go Paul go Paul it's
like [ __ ] I do not feel like listening
to
this now now I know you're a
streamer it's okay guys that was the
hardest team now
[Music]
turn I literally just don't look at chat
like for the rest of my teammates I
literally I minimized the window I just
play the game now it's
easy I got it it's for them that's
respectable that you know what that's
true we got the hardest team out of the
way the five alley kicks in the dream
right
here what the [ __ ] shin is that like hi
than
G what is she doing my Lobby I'm a
baby bro I literally just fought eam
leave me
alone
[Laughter]
round leave me the [ __ ] alone I really
had to fight what the [ __ ] okay I got
confused too I'm
sorry oh my my God please I had to fight
eam get out of my
[Laughter]
Lobby
okay oh God no
no let's go team round all right here
you go God they really [ __ ] The Vibes
up only thing is when winners lose it's
like it's like God
it's like God is turned down his head it
doesn't make sense what how did she
scept that I'm like fighting again it's
going to happen eventually go there's
only so long you can go without [ __ ]
losing dude I'm waiting for
it like I don't think it's going to be a
big deal I don't care about it I think
it's going to happen against FD you guys
saw that [ __ ] lag dude oh yeah yeah
yeah kind of
lag I think it might be like a console
issue or something
all right like that
[ __ ] oh my God oh my God how did I [ __ ]
that up how did I [ __ ] that up how did I
[ __ ] that up of course it's me of course
that's how I [ __ ] it up leave me
[Laughter]
alone oh my God
please just f i just not F EAP get
out get out
oh my god get the [ __ ] out of
here I almost had it I did not almost
had it you know
that get ready for the next battle it's
going to be hard no I don't want it to
be harder I want to get it
easily no
F I'm like three games from Blue oh you
did you promote I'm close I'm I'm I'm
halfway to purple if I could get blue
before Sunday I you know that would feel
nice I feel like you just might as well
just [ __ ] strive for it that's easy
you know oh my
God leave me alone leave me alone look
at that you learn how to play Tekken you
better play
Tekken please give leave me alone
please I had to fight e please leave me
alone
round
two fight it's not
fair this is actually not
fair bro what the [ __ ] are we doing
here all right mental
shattered no I was waiting before to
fight
him no what did he do to me
what did he do to
[Laughter]
me m boom he boomed the mental how how
is this
possible he he lives went free in my
head there we go oh God not
AO there yeah that should hit right no
how did I not
hit there you go that [ __ ]
hit the eam
Cur fight hey
bro I I laughed it before but I honestly
I forgot I know that o can literally
like go the rid art Midway so it's not
sidewalk oh my God but if you are going
to step it is it left or right bro [ __ ]
off pretty sure
it's best to SCP and then block so in
case he does level two you can still
launch that yeah yeah
fight okay this is the other combo he
delayed got getting up that my thing
didn't even hit that's crazy that's
actually crazy I didn't expect that holy
[ __ ] is he going duck no he didn't duck
thank
god oh thank God he didn't duck either
no no no no no no no no no no no oh no
do I get up from that he
missed
yes okay not
intentional wait did I not get that
point did he unplug before oh okay
I
yeah I did not intentionally save
that but I'll take it I'll take
it oh thank
God how did you do the Forbidden I did
the forbid I don't I didn't know I did
it it's called but and mashing I Got a
notification get ready for the next
battle thank God for butt mashing
did he actually played yeah I don't
think it's up yet oh yep Lobby's
up no I just got in the game okay I'm I
I'll finish this rank match quick as
then I lose really quick round
one
fight all right come
on yeah boom boom boom yeah please let
me win no please
yes all round when did this happen
fight when did my neighbor get a drum
set
what you're like oh this is going to be
fun moving forward oh no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no he got his sorry
I my mic
on oh it's cool it's
funny no ah my God
okay let's
join
no I'll be in in one
second oh my God he [ __ ] up he [ __ ]
me up it's okay I didn't want to be red
anyway I didn't I didn't want to be red
anyway guys oh my
God wait he predicted that how
how did he predict that my job is to
beat bang way round Let's go Team I
believe in all of
you oh my God not playing that that well
don't worry it's okay we lock in it's
okay lock in we lock we all lock in
and okay don't worry about it man it's
not even a oh I red the red okay I'm
goinging in
let's go
I'm
yeah I'm [ __ ] go goodbye
sir I'm I'm locked in I got
red all right where is the D I [ __ ]
had it all right crab let's fine if I
lose or win don't wor honestly like me
too I feel like I'm playing like weird
all right guys for once in my life I'll
hide the
passcode holy [ __ ] I'm going to do it
guys DOI she's not even ranked that much
higher than you to be honest very wable
yeah but I feel like she actually knows
what she's doing because she played this
game much
longer I feel like she knows more than
seven moves
all right guys you can't blame me if
somebody joins this Lobby I I actually
hit the
code it's not me this time oh you did
I'm I'm not putting in that much effort
I'll say
it I gave up say jam has a toe like the
whole world's upside
down what are these rumors of slime it's
not a rumor everyone in the fgc knows
this knows what that sjam has a toupe
really yeah yeah it's real he's like
Hitman bald oh my God why his hair so
much I know why does he
care if you're bald you're smarter cuz
you mold so
much really what I'm saying extra bra
space
man he his chat was probably making fun
of him for being bald so he went and got
a
toue it's good then you can rub it for
good luck you think Avatar is the goat
exactly he'd be crazy if I in
games bro he he's wearing a TP cuz he's
hiding his power that's why he's not a
pro
player that's that's the brocc was he
can't be a pro he's not he doesn't
commit oh
man no wonder you Sam is so good oh my
God no wonder he's so good cuz he's
bald it's
true yeah eam does get the weird Bal
buff also why I'm the best in the world
at
this what
we what are you waiting for y'all can go
ahead and start okay fight let me in
sk's sk's oh we were waiting for oh he
woke up look he woke up I was like who
are we waiting for finally I can show
the
screen's go you can't yell at me guys if
if somebody joins the
lobby okay but I hate playing as Raina
though she's so fast she's so [ __ ]
fast I'm too
bulky Just Two Reds duking it out that's
what you love to see honest gaming this
is this is
true this is what I'm here
for wait what was her weak I I don't
remember what her weakness was coach you
didn't tell
[Laughter]
me uh coach what do I
do R sh talk about S no we
didn't we never R your [ __ ] run your
[ __ ] let's go
what do I do coach that's your [ __ ] wait
who that just do that do what that that
you're doing it right now you
doing it literally just happened it just
happened you just did all I did that I
did that fight holy [ __ ] oh my God I did
that did you see that
coach good yeah okay I think she knows
now she knows now I feel like time to
use that mid yep time to hit that oh
wait the square yeah when you're in the
Sprint it's okay it's time
oh no [ __ ]
way we're not pressing down one
time once huh what do you mean I
told no one ever expects it wait she do
she actually oh she's mixing it up yeah
she's mixing it up wow smart player
there's no way no what is this mental
block I don't know they never AA like
there's no way weird they they get it
and then they lose it yeah I don't
understand either I don't understand why
they
don't okay you and the Slime and you
need to learn take a book out of [ __ ]
toki's P know rip that [ __ ]
right finish it she doed she dued nice
nice try nice
try
fight remember you can do that running
knee if okay I I was trying to but then
like I tried to but like I pressed the I
pressed
Square okay yes oh God
yes oh no I couldn't
oh nice RAR oh she got it oh it's too
strong oh oh the
misery oh the misery wait
what oh my God I N I I hate that move
though in
rank oh what
okay hey
nice okay
big okay mix up okay
dud I got it I got I got you got it I
got a set let's go I did
it oh that was good job that was close
25 hours dookie versus 100 hour R SK is
definitely at 125
now cof baby versus bom yeah Hy
M get
B oh my
God it's okay nice he said you're five
times
better you don't want to see doy bird at
125 hours yeah you don't want to see 100
I don't think I have the hours for that
either to be fair suplex okay no way I
just nope I like how you didn't hop kick
either that was good yeah that was good
oh my god dude
feel they're going to learn this by the
finals though looking like a pretty good
move bro how does it feel saying like
that was pretty
good oh my god dude good actually she's
[ __ ] swagging this is
crazy only correct decision what the
[ __ ] only correct decision how do she
keep getting away with this new
moves like Devil May Cry
how does she keep getting away oh
big oh no I don't know when it's she
like [ __ ] mixes it up so it's hard
nice oh
no
goodbye
she oh
no that's fine that's fine she she had
to use lightning herself to kill you
just to be clear hey we start off with
that
[ __ ] round start Al
kick you're about to get King's worst
low
nerfed just of what I do not show this
to Hara hara's watching I guarantee you
right now oh my God oh my God what do
you think that was intentional for her
that [ __ ] was like a movie yeah holy
[ __ ] okay when you pop heat hold on to
your heat smash don't pop it right away
cuz she's blocking it just hold on to it
for a little bit
okay oh [ __ ] oh I think she actually is
learning yeah that was a good adapation
we're still alive still alive oh my boom
all right that's big do I do square or
grab uh you run up grab
okay let's get it big re wait till she
gets up though wait till she gets up cuz
sometimes they like stay stay on the
ground there you go bro there you go
there you go I pop heat easy easy pop
heat when she get Smash and go mid
Square square no M bad read M oh nice
try nice try nice
try a plan is worse is better than no
plan at all
Matt's Matt's fault it's Matt's fault
blew it yeah you blew it you blew it for
I can only be read so many times I'm
sorry the do that running grab a lot she
has not Ted a single one
and then she's and it's going to be a
bad read
again oh my God what the [ __ ] how oh my
God she mad she mad now the bounce okay
she [ __ ] mad
now she's [ __ ]
mad oh my God she's so mad I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry she's going to block this
no
way all right true true true said it all
there round
two fight
okay I like the idea we playing Tekken
this is we're playing Tekken yeah right
here right now grab right now this is
Tekken oh [ __ ] oh yeah this is
definitely
taken nice I love your patience this is
so good yeah
oh I think I need to be more patient
guys that's beautiful hug what God I
thought you pressed it's okay still
alive no she actually blocked it it's
okay and in the end I got that one
set not over that's true that's
true wait what what was that I don't
know but Frey yeah that looked [ __ ]
freaky though freaky techniques yeah
that's a freaky technique though not
going to lie8 is real in here
yeah okay that's a freaky [ __ ] teque
a lot ofage oh [ __ ] I should have
grabbed guys it's okay I got us that
Five Points though
got wait we get points per per game do
we get per no in the beginning no oh we
don't this
time no
no I should have used more alley kicks I
I blame M kicks probably probably would
have made her knees explode true she
would have been a Smoking Pair of Shoes
in the Coliseum so
true what's the code for this Lobby it
doesn't let me spectate so I restart it
how do I say it to you without leaking
it's 8921 oh I guess it doesn't matter
yeah I we did this [ __ ] yesterday I'm
so
stupid right
there who's next wants to play
everyone he will not play R2 let's go
con I should have Ali kicked more let's
go goat Let's Go
goat come out con bring it back Redeem
Me Oh I got a good stage o it's uh the
comet asteroid whatever it
is floor blast on the third round yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah she's always going to start off
with that uh side step round one
shoulder fight I hate fighting her in
rink yeah she can
R oh got
it Island Con Island Cony come on
con the Bas
nice round two the coach didn't teach
her that they will by the tournament
time y yeah definitely do you think
they're you you're so cute right now
oh yeah I'm just going to abuse that oh
my God oh my God get your points that's
just our uh layer one so it's okay
right round three
fight tried to go uh the muscle Buster
do yeah it would exploded the wall of
the
floors that's what I'm trying to land
here I don't want to try to force it too
much
though what the [ __ ] oh my God she broke
it
wow got it it's resing butt that was
insane yeah your regular combo now oh
sorry more time I got I got I got it
more time there
if she's smart she'll switch the
change yeah cuz you can but I mean I
didn't
earlier I don't think has anyone
actually swapped a stage round I don't
think so yeah I think we're just Auto
piling now this I would I would just be
like y rematch go again I lose I win all
right all right M but you didn't you
never
lost I will
eventually you'll need a SW SES you
don't
lose
yeah
nice got it let's go back three baby
down back three she's just really scared
fight yeah oh my God
so I can just control Pace oh oh my
goodness I'm going to do that to SK in
the finals yep oh she doesn't take giy
swing oh God bro you're
nuts if she's struggling to me now is Al
like like she's scrambling to find an
opening so if I just swing every time
it's like I don't know I think her brain
scrambled yeah there's no
very annoying so I get it or not the
match up but I guess King yeah King is
annoying
[ __ ] she's breaking every yeah she's
breaking counter hit throws too do is
she mashing or is she actually knowing
the tech well she's broken both twos and
threes or twos and ones so and this
might and one plus two yeah she nice job
all right okay just assume it won't be
that free in Final but I appreciate the
points lightweight baby yeah he has to
teach her that like that should not hit
like just lay down you
know all right let me read my Fang notes
Fang way all right you got good I
believe in
you
okay oh wait was it this guy I think it
was this guy right or am I thinking of
Ray uh one of the fairlite is the Fang
who is pretty hard okay we talked about
it remember uh slime he's going to lay
down in a lot of Oki situations when you
like to do the running one plus two so
that's a forward forward two
yep and don't start the round with the
buttons he's always waiting for you
okay maybe you can start with like a
down back two maybe if you really want
something and back one plus two hunting
bear stands one plus two will probably
get this guy look at the cause how do I
get in there uh who is unban me bro who
the [ __ ] is that how are they
getting
so so [ __ ] I want you to know that
you will you will never be valued from
from the people that you watch every day
ever remember
like well we know the leak's not coming
from us for sure it's coming from inside
the brawl Pro
it's like what it's our it's actually
our alt accounts by the
way it's one of
us I like at least he's sitting on the
sidelines like he's not yeah he's not in
yeah holding the the lobby
hostage all right let's do it baby oh
that's a new costume
is that a Punisher round oh my god he
has a
gun maybe it's Jason there's that snake
Edge W this guy's a
nerd do
that nice
job got stop doing that mixing it up
job it's way careful all right time to
mix it time to mix
it round wait
fight oh my
God what the [ __ ] where did your HP go
two grab that's a one or two you could
have killed him if you did the wall
combo yeah
KO
round
fight okay we got
this oh my
god there it is there it
is there we go that's okay good [ __ ]
nice yeah oh jig didn't
work round
four
fight
Jesus
no I thought he do a low he just kep a
running one can I step that
if I KN uh not if yeah if as but if you
if he hits you with it and it knocks you
down and then you tag then probably not
he just shouldn't do that pose when he's
teing I mean if you can react to it you
block that you can twin piston it okay
too is really bad that
shoulder round
one
fight oh my my
God we have to threaten the hunting bear
grab
oh I'm really bad [ __ ] all right is
definitely he's definitely overwhelming
for sure
that was
sick you can also that roll guard
break no
way I would definitely rard him after he
does something like that like a heat
burst you have it he's mashing every
time
oops
okay yeah he's breaking one plus two
every
time oh the punish
oh oh my God go
slim
oh Kuma good
dive
fight that
work boom boom boom
boom always grabbing from OK when he get
up
I didn't know do another [ __ ]
kick what a miserable [ __ ] character
he's a strong player we played last time
he was taking not sets but he was taking
rounds off of me like why would you play
the character that does that
pose for I was thinking last match I was
thinking that makes you think like what
are you really about man yeah
yeah to say going to say it like know
I'm saying that's
all are they updating the points live or
probably not right probably not
nah gotta here we go laggy as [ __ ] Eddie
Zina I want to say it like I'll
definitely try but I like this
guy on microwave man I don't know we'll
try it's okay if he you're lagging he's
lagging this is like literally like the
most ranked Tekken match I've ever
experienced like one bar Eddie
Jack oh no Jack he said [ __ ] your
character oh I saw him in the general
last night he said this was going to be
a jack off oh my God I'm not kidding he
said he going to learn Jack Jack off
yes that's what he said is this real oh
my God the Jack mirror did he give up no
he play The Undertaker bro oh that is
the under father gascoin bloodborne
whatever his name
is oh my
God that's [ __ ]
right a jack
off okay don't do
that understood
God I'm jacking off
like he's jacking it he's jacking it
wait what wait what what do you guys
mean by that wa when you first yeah
who you know in the race of
jacks what were you thinking about you
nice
R jaag him harder
Ok please no it's true he's got to Jack
as hard as he
can you can't look this heart somebody's
going to start a
fire you got to look him in the
eyes oh we're distracting him we should
stop
round maybe nice nice
duck [ __ ] yeah counter hit blue spark
everything
dong
yeah oh that was sick that was
so he's springing a
lot
round
fight D the double
Jackman no way oh
nice great
thr let's go nice counter hit dude [ __ ]
get back on head good
[ __ ] back
on throwing a set
away why we throwing the set away all
right yeah leave the lobby all right
some calling the Jack hamy don't do that
I know I know like you got a lot of
Tekken experience under your years and
[ __ ] but new game just play Eddie I want
I want to
fight what the [ __ ] I don't know why you
picked Jack on me man well remember when
we were going to water viiew him uh I
know he did play Jack
yeah very Legacy Jack not a single gamma
how yeah oh my [ __ ] God I hate this
guy all right BR I actually need your
help
oh oh remember that power Crush oh [ __ ]
thank you mytical
so you pressure him you can
yeah
[Music]
okay I will
hold a Saina why do they play Such
freaky characters I've not
seen say the team she's so freaky watch
watch she'll get on the ground it's a
freak Festival is it the one where she
climbs on like a spider yeah yeah yeah
and she I hate
her okay oh oh uhoh
uhoh oh my God what a genius what a
genius
nice ooh send him to space
Jack you're going into
orbit round
two fight
that's not
fair spamming is banned somebody should
tell him no no no we Aly kicks have been
paying us pretty well mind
bck we need the alley kicks I almost B
on alley kicks
alone the fact that it worked like not
once but three times in a row was what
surprised me is she
doing if you stepped on her head she
would
die why is she doing that that is not an
advantageous
position like a
watermelon oo she weighs like 110
lb all right never mind I'm Not Afraid
Of Z we get one punch let's go 58
defense my goat 58 defense eight that's
two right I knock
again well there's one more one more
yeah you won dude yeah sorry so I'm good
I leave yeah yeah okay okay all right
dude if I lose a third coach match I
need a therapy session there okay it's
okay I will give you the biggest hug at
Evo we're going to be there anyway don't
worry about it it's all right let's all
get dinner bro let's go to Evo YY I was
trying I was trying to figure out like a
good [ __ ] dinner spot so I was going
to hit you guys up be like hey you want
to where is Evo this year yeah I'm down
dude it's in Evo every year do doy are
you going to go or no I don't know are
we going to win
I I love that response that is
good super I think he's going to go too
so we should invite him to dinner
yeah you got this my goat my uncle my
dad my everything man come on coach this
is it got to bring it
home that's right I'll study up for the
Turning like on the in two days from now
I see my mistakes like they'll duck like
a grab and then I'll lose like half my
life and then they'll Oki situation me
and then it's rough out here man these
guys are
good how did they improve so fast I
don't understand ready for Steve this
time you're to
stop all I'm going to close my chat Ste
we'll be your
chat we'll be your chat don't worry is
that Bayonetta
on Steven that's
Ste Bon and Gender Bend
fight
M it's
over damn
it oh it's
Kojima oh
maybe Pima doesn't wear pajama
bottoms don't know Pima on break
no more playing
around good
[ __ ] I like the little
push nice
nice that's the [ __ ] I'm talking about
baby I'm not sure round
three
fight over
here damn
oh freaky Steve I'll say
it it's just us against the freaky
Army that's it every team just studied
our gameplay only the world of
degenerates
around
[ __ ] oh ni nice nice
okay love punch him in the
N
oh good [ __ ]
nice Tekken I love how it's like chicken
playing chicken right
now
nice let's go good [ __ ] nice all kick
baby Alli kick baby
kick baby hell yeah good ass move we get
we get distributions from Big alley
kick the Aly kick
[Music]
clutch that's a wall Steven take him to
that
wall
[ __ ] bro is
counting o oh
how does he do it nice how does he [ __ ]
do the [ __ ] I'm talking about man we
need this what the [ __ ] Parry dude the
[ __ ] was that move let's
go that move at the end
ow would hurt blood is a boxer they
don't do that [ __ ] in his ring round
come on attack
in go baby I don't even know what this
move is take that what the [ __ ] may be
one of
these oh it's like a
chiropractic just going to make a little
adjustment keep
dies
nice
UPA play around
this guy's not playing around
anymore he keep saying that oh oh what
was a
clinch it doesn't matter go give me some
three headman
[Laughter]
chat beans
sausage oh my
oh I'm sa love me cross simple
ass oh no way oh what that was so weird
that so we
yeah oh good oh
no no
around coach get up
coach oh
man wow wow that was SI oh my God that
was nice that was okay that was good for
him
fight oh
nice I'm so [ __ ] funny that his
that's his off military
com nice he so clean with the
floats he's doing it oh play around
buy nice okay one more one more that's
for your life good [ __ ] nice job good
[ __ ] bro bro let's go I love you an
final round let's get this done
fight oh look at all these
blocks smash
nice
yeah bust his
ass oh wow
oh oh yes oh take him to the wall yes
real freaky hours we're in the basement
now wall we get the wall what we k
w yes call him wall Pro oh he blocked
that oh he nap yeah he has to rest a
little he's got no clutch bone no clutch
bone what the [ __ ] did he just
do oh I
pressed no nice ni
nice that was a good
rage yeah yeah that was good that was a
really good rage [ __ ] all right welcome
that was a good fight though that was
good yeah was that was a really good
match actually I was insane
mhm round one come on download fight
he's only 26 Daniels you're 100
Daniels over here you win this you'll be
120 Daniels mhm you steal his Daniels
yeah those Daniels need a new home
oh oh
wow nice
break that was
unfortunate round
two fight over here oh
no more play
around
nice oh [ __ ]
oh my God those Ducks let's
go it's like he actually knows how to
play Tekken
fight nice oh my God that
camera
oh it's his alley kick his brain is
scrambled his brain is scrambled the
alley kick no one knows what to do his
brain is
scrambled do it
again go let's [ __ ] go I think he's
scramble bro take it
home he saw what I did to SK and he got
worried brother's brain is hot right
now oh W that was a good side
St nice nice
God I'm talking about
yeah yes the
[Applause]
bomb let's go coach yes take the wi
that's what you thought good [ __ ] dude
oh not even close not even close it's
cuz he used to play melee yeah H the sh
bro he he's got that actual unbreakable
mental okay his name is braw proo to be
clear all right I think we claim him
congratulating him on his first win
today his first win yeah thank you thank
youy welcome to the club join the
club the join the winner Club
[ __ ] [ __ ] nice job hey we kind of did
well yeah
[ __ ] yeah we take those we take those
a positive record especially you know
five points per that's big yeah yeah
yeah
yeah all right yeah we're looking good
so far on because we did
41 uh let me see
4-14 but then 32 so we're in a good
spot I freaky G also we got the hardest
team out of the way so yeah yeah yeah
yeah don't say that didn't what if like
you're going to Karm us bro for you for
me just like all teams are the same I
got all demons every single day of my
life I'm F them I'm falling you be them
all you haven't lost yet Jack I will be
losing literally been saying that for
two slams it's his Strat it's like his
his like reverse Jinx it's actually
impossible for me to lose because if I
lose then I'll say yeah I told you guys
I would lose but if I don't then I look
like a [ __ ]
god heed
this but yeah I'll be losing soon I'm
sure don't say that don't say that cuz
what if that happens in the finals scar
random I [ __ ] hate we got Scar and
amas you guys saw how they were playing
armor hopkick armor dick jab every
defensive option ever like I got to make
a read on what the [ __ ] they're going to
do like you guys read
not me
man I brain Rod away playing OverWatch
and teeken
and do we have a while till the next one
yeah do we have a while not sure I'm
going to go get some water and uh use a
bathroom little refresher all
right time to practice taken round one
yeah let me see these clips one second
oh my God I'm playing as a tenr now I'm
too high rank I don't belong
[Applause]
here
y round guys I don't belong in this ELO
I literally lucked out on this
I brw forc my way into this
ELO like Lally have not been playing
that much Tekken I'm pretty I I don't
think I belong
[Laughter]
here oh no please leave me
alone I don't even know how to
juggle that's how how I don't belong
[Laughter]
here I don't even know how to juggle
people
yay whoops that was an
accident who whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa here you go
yay carried by Aly kicks bro some people
spend their entire lives [ __ ]
grinding to this ELO I don't know how I
get
here that's the saddest
part some people spent their entire
lives getting here I just
existed i al kicked my way to Victory
[Laughter]
I I think like including the including
like the games now I think I have 30
hours on Tekken 30 hours on Tekken for
red rank it just works just
do told you I don't I don't belong here
the moment I learned a four like a fifth
and sixth move I I went up two rings
like yesterday I was at I think
Dominator I think yesterday I was at
Dominator I think I started at Dominator
or something get for the and then in
like and then when I learned the fifth
and sixth move I went up to Red so like
every move unlocks the
ring round one she keeps getting a wa I
don't know how I don't know how I keep
doing it it's actually crazy like I
literally don't don't know what I'm
doing
like I I should not be getting away with
this is this the same guy is it I'm
sorry