about the [ __ ] are you
doing
God coach what are you doing good [ __ ]
if I do that you'll be mad at
me what the [ __ ] do as I say not as I
do hey I didn't want to put the pressure
on you I think we're second seed cuz you
won that cuz we
won [ __ ] dude I didn't want to say [ __ ]
but like that was the tiebreaker
really you got it you got some
tiebreaker dude oh my God that is why we
tell you after you won I didn't want to
say it but they're first seed and we're
second yeah we literally just like last
time we got we got a seed we got lost I
know I was silent I was like I said I
didn't say it you closed the chat bro
close the chat con and I had like a link
we just knew that it would not be good
to say yeah don't say that [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] nice good [ __ ] [ __ ] oh my God
literally all
performed Yay good [ __ ] [ __ ] guys we so
happy I'm so happy we earned it we
earned the [ __ ] second SE oh my God
we did came back at the end
yes that's great we don't have to do
anything for the first match let's go
[ __ ] [ __ ] guys we get to chill we get
to scout get by yep we get to watch
thank God so proud of you guys man so
proud that was [ __ ] sick well done it
was incredible everybody came together
it was all the sets were so close too
[ __ ] man y clutched
it clutched it bro so and they all
trained against us they actually studied
us that's true actually yeah they did a
lot oh my God yeah they actually did
their homework dude did you know last
last time the tiebreaker was against NK
also really for the Evo tickets Evo yeah
that was against better bro you're just
better all right we uh I think we're
second seed nice wow we got a lot of
work to do we got a lot of work to do
for tomorrow after yes and this time
bravoo will teach
Matt Oh wait we're third seed oh never
mind we're third seed never mind what
after four that's crazy after 41 okay we
four we'll cook that's okay I'm not
worried about second or third we play
another set but like you know don't
don't worry about it don't just don't
just just imagine for second okay never
let let the king players do
math ride ride the high ride the High
told me it was second my bad yo I can't
believe it believing the chat the chat
got me killed the other day you're right
you're right my bad can't listen to him
right second in our
heart unless it comes down like a
weird what yeah what are the points
looking like I want to look no yeah cuz
we're 141
we were tied with kfm Tony yeah they're
crunching the okay we'll see now s
confirmed for a second I don't like this
wait now they could be gaslighting oh
for a second they're
saying let me let me play teken I will
dominate let me play Tekken ball wait s
messed up I what I reach yet stop stop
stop hold on I'm Banning you actually
like never leave chat except
for the spreadsheet
wait yeah wait if we had more if we had
if us and myk had the same amount of
points today but we had one more Point
Wednesday right oh yeah yeah I mean it's
it's additive so I don't we're second
we're tied for second if it's Tekken
ball put me
on they're saying we're tied for second
but they didn't include yesterday so
we're second including yesterday's
points
apparently that's what s j
said if me and myk are tied we should
get it cuz I just beat the coach the
coach match just happened real real I
should get it because it was [ __ ]
stressful wait second by three points oh
we're second by three points let's go
second by three points let's [ __ ] so
doesn't that mean literally ifon first
yesterday then we would have Tekken ball
yes oh my God you guys clutched it out
yesterday or
dude oh my God yesterday yesterday was
all that matters because we got first
yes last literally on Wednesday and why
K is in third now
yay who do we play against roller
coaster I was so ready to Tekken ball it
up dude I got strategies that I don't
want to talk about I don't want to tell
you guys how grinded that [ __ ] Wednesday
actually mattered three-point diff
that's crazy literally a one game
difference that literally literally
means everyone who won like
every single everyone matter good
[ __ ] [ __ ] let's go this is so sick
because like everyone on the team like
it contributes
not oh I can hear Josh talking so so
when is someone going to name drop
super ready a lot bigger streak Than
Ready W more
game I love the guy but I I feel like
the doky bird special the alley kick
special that's oh yeah soon as we learn
block that Yoshi the spin a Roy [ __ ]
it's easy yeah the moment I block that
it's over I can alley kick
forever you think they're going to learn
how to block the alley kick guys we were
only two points away from first also
[ __ ] done it yeah if we won one more set
against but I mean first or second
doesn't yeah it doesn't matter it
doesn't it doesn't matter right we're
just on the other side of the bracket
from my understanding
don't does it matter IFK our third seed
then we just for1 them so like you know
not in a bad
spot
okay good I'm going to ask I'm going to
ask stage one see if anyone wants to
play t and also uh we don't have once
the bracket comes out we don't have to
focus on like five characters cuz we we
we get a buy yeah maybe we might with
the loser bracket I don't know how that
works have to prepare yeah for whatever
comes
up yeah I think it's mathematically will
be less characters to focus on the
moment you teach me how to block I'm
unstoppable yeah know yeah we'll do all
that like it'll be a read but by
definition we have to lab against like
at least one less
team oh good [ __ ] guys well done today
seriously hell yeah wow crazy
this is really like rough on the mental
I'm not going to lie dude my brain
unironically
hurts and the thing like I don't I don't
know it's just Pride because like we're
already
going excuse me here
too you just don't want to let your
friends down it's so hard exactly like I
don't want to let you guys down you know
I mean but like at the same time does it
matter yeah we're already going wait ex
hello guys hello
is
hello go we can we can create a [ __ ]
like a little a little thing a group
thing we'll just all P because you're
part of the team too true yeah let's do
it for DOI though that's the first
option then then then we'll do a
donation drive for a millionaire after
first option is we try and get top two
I'm not going to use my own
money but one by two
points oh I would have led beat Josh's
team so bad you beat Josh bro would have
been
firsten I lost to his no it is just it's
just I choked too guys it's okay we all
each of us choked at least once guys
it's okay it's a team
effort second though as a team effort
yeah yeah my Chad is saying give her sup
ticket that's what my what I'm
saying it over super pay for his own
ticket I gave away my first ticket cuz I
already had a Evo [ __ ] like I already
had a ticket oh what the [ __ ] yeah I was
like here sjm just give it to someone
else sjm saves money if uh if we win
yeah so it's in his interest to rig the
bracket oh that's true that's true oh
look at how close we were dude oh my oh
my God we were so close that's crazy if
B you know knock going wi not going to
happen but if we don't get top two we'll
all pitch get Doki to Evo too yeah
because I mean clutch master Doki
literally every match mattered in Doki
clutch that [ __ ] wa the my set counted
yeah won Mattern that's literally the
reason got there's no way I don't like
you deserve to be an EVO yay I got
points from SK yeah you [ __ ] you
literally farmed
well every set mattered I don't think
every match right I don't how did it
work every match turns into every set
and every set matters okay okay okay so
you got points off the guys you beat
yeah yeah yeah wait off the points like
I got sets off yeah so how many people
did you beat in a set it was like a
couple
right I beat a more but then I got set
off SK and gloomy you went like uh what
like 2 three 32 two three
yeah so like literally that's that's
actually a Difference Maker like it's
crazy
W that ra that that King eats match with
he's
growling
yay that's a good clip that was a really
it was like right as he looked into the
camera it was very
funny in the air did you see it did you
see the clip no Chad send it send me the
clip please it's extremely [ __ ] funny
my my POV yeah hold on here you go I'm
going to post it in the thing want to
see it is extremely good hold on uh here
you go watch this put this on
stream
yay
title all right okay I'm gonna go get
food congratulations everyone holy [ __ ]
later we the goats oh you R yeah
uncle are you staying live me uh I mean
what am I going to do I guess I'll stay
live for like 30 minutes or something
sure all right we'll give braw
Pro I'll the so
enthusiastic okay okay I'm going give
hold on let me get my 90 second ad ready
hold on oh yeah yeah get the ad Revenue
I'm ready I'm ready all right good [ __ ]
Bro all right guys GG's everybody I'll
pop a raid see you in two days later
GG's guys yeah we'll train we'll train
bro let's
get what let's [ __ ] get see me in
purple
rank
G's oh my God guys we got second I got
to set up es SK and go it's an
improvement I got to say off almost
everybody oh my God braa is [ __ ]
jamming it out right now guys it's okay
in the finals we're definitely going to
have our new pc
and the shackles will be off for
real and we got red rank on stream
too guys we got red rank on
stream to be fair I feel like I've been
I honestly feel like I brute forced a
red rank because all I did was just do
the moves I know and then leave
I
just I just do like the most tilting
[ __ ] moves that nobody has ever seen
before I call it the Doki special with
five alley kicks and then into a hop
kick red red is red these people in
those rigs did not know what they
saw the one I'm pretty sure I tilted a
lot of people I was so surprised
surprised that the match against SK was
so close because she had so many hours
ahead of me all I I like hard grinded
the last this week but like ESI still
had so many hours ahead of me like
everybody had so many hours ahead of me
um throughout this tournament so I felt
like I definitely grew a lot in such a
short amount of time and uh and I did I
don't like I don't def I just go in
Yolo the monkey
I feel like I caught up really fast in
the short amount of hours I think I have
like 30 hours in total at the moment in
Tekken for now but I'm like I um and
it's my first fighting game so I'm
really happy with my progress so far
like I never expected to get red rank at
all so I'm super happy with my
progress and I honestly think the moment
I learn how to block it's [ __ ] over
for everybody that's that's my only
problem the moment I learn the block and
I become more patient it's over I I I
figured it out because I win the mental
game like I I win the mind games off of
people because when they fight against
me it's so I can feel the rage I can
feel people being really angry when
they're fighting against me because my
moods are so [ __ ] [ __ ] like
my boo are still are so [ __ ] and I
can tell people are very
mad you see them get more aggressive oh
hell yeah yeah I can feel that they're
deafening and like going hard Focus I
can feel it I just need to like I just
need to learn how to block and it's over
like block alley kick alley kick jump
kick bam done they
better hey guys I hope you guys enjoyed
today's uh event we got second place
overall it was so close too we're second
place overall that's really I'm really
proud of my team and I'm happy that um
my sets actually contributed to cuz I
thought like since I only won one game
that that was it I only contributed one
game but like I'm happy that my sets
actually mattered and it actually
contributed into the score overall so
like I'm glad that uh I'm happy that it
actually helped the team with the score
so yeah y cuz I didn't lose both sets I
like won like one out of like a set
which is why why I'm
happy hey guys I'm going to call it here
I'm going to like relax a little bit get
some back behind the scenes work done um
and then I'll start training again
tomorrow as always everybody stay
hydrated posture check get up and move
around to get that blood flowing any of
you stay up for me head to bed cuz you
deserve it I'll see you guys next time
everybody bye guys M bye by
[Music]